I feel like I've been locked out Spent my soul in a way I shouldn't have thought out
A part of my brain was fried I thought that I could win but the chat just sighed
Won't you banish me? They said I wasn't reasonable nothing was debatable
What they didn't see is that I am still me
knock myself out. Oh, shit. Hi. Oh, good morning. Let's see.
I need to fix the camera. Okay. Hello, guys.
Mmm, am I hungry? I think I'm kind of hungry.
Well, how about we have breakfast? Hey, what's up? It's Friday. Hey, it's Friday, right?
Good morning, you're like an old man. Oh, like if I like a look at that you're actually I'm a cold and then I'm like
younger from that side
Right. I don't know what it why doesn't my beard go?
All white at once like why is it like half white?
Not weird. Mmm. Let's see
The Arthur
It's really funny like some people come in I think oh well because it's like they come in and they leave real quick
I won't even tell what they do, but there is nothing not nice to me
Thinking of getting a stone
I'm doing my show so
Where they do that this they dislike the stream
Unfortunately, I have a large
larger than I'd like
Portion of dislikes like
Lately so I think some it's especially because I like I
Will I don't know. I think it's the same person just on multiple accounts. It's just annoying
but
Not really. It's fine
So that's why it's really important. Just hit the like guys if you want to hit the like
You know, that's so I mean not the dislike, right? I don't think it matters and no one's everyone says it doesn't matter
I'm trying to figure out. I was on Tommy James show last night and
There is this
Like younger woman, you know
Younger woman there and she was like it just she just reminded me of that woman Shannon
Like it was like they just talked the same kind of the same and she was like you're at
F-A-G-G-O-T you're going to hell and she just kept screaming it over and over and over
I mean, it's like I would play it but I
Don't want to get like in trouble. I mean, it's like she was just going off on me
But then I was like, you know, and I kind of fought back like I did with Shannon and eventually she's just like
I don't know if she rage quit but she but she wasn't a rage the whole time
But uh, she's a huge she didn't leave and I was like, okay
I thought he kicked her.
By the way, Tommy was cool, and yeah.
Did you guys see, what do you think of this picture?
I don't know if you saw this on my post,
but I made this picture.
I generated myself.
I was like, what would I look like as a beautiful woman?
Do I have it?
Oh, shit.
I don't know if I have it.
I don't know if I have I mean I can go get I can show you actually right here share
Check this out
What do you think and so the question is smash or pass guys I
was
Look, but look look how I would like I mean, I don't know if I look like this, but
What do you think oh
Okay, yeah, I mean I mean I would look like this if I like had like a lot of great
Makeup and surgery or something look
Arthur what do you think?
No, happy Fredgers Friday, Missy Elliott Monday or no, it's Friday. Yeah, happy Fredgers Friday
I don't know. I know LD is in town. That'd be cool if I could go hang out with him and his friends. That'd be pretty cool. Oh and my
My sights looking pretty good too. I want to show that to you guys too
Let me see if I can get some food
Hungry. What do you think guys? I want to slowly
Come on, I'm pretty hot
You got to admit I look pretty good as a email, right?
You think Arthur
Yeah
Oh good God good God
Everyone's speechless. Oh, no, everyone's leaving. I'm not everyone
Okay
Is there a deal oh, I don't see a deal on this one. Oh shit, that might not be good. There's not a deal. I'm not gonna get it
Four dollars and credits if I take a photo of my receipt I claim that right now
I already had it. Oh, no, no. I need to go. I need to die dying out. I
Matt the restaurant. No, no, no delivery
It's a reach I would so
You don't think I would look like her if I shave please you don't seem I that's what I look like
But that's my face when I was younger shut up or what a hell
I'm so hot
Okay, anyway, maybe I wouldn't but who knows
Let me have a fantasy. Okay, I'm not gonna ever do it
You have to you have to say I oh, it's a reach you could say. Oh, no, you're hot. You're beautiful, John mean the psyche
Oh my god, I get everyone's fucking leave and come on. Okay. Everyone's a dick. I don't like you guys
River left everyone who stays you're fine
If it takes off 30% not I'm done. Oh
No, I didn't
Way too expensive so never not ever didn't order that again
Where's all the wrinkles? Well, I mean it's like called makeup. Okay. It's called makeup
Add some cats to her background, no tricks is probably back there. I mean that is my background
I mean, I just took my basically took my photo and then I said make me a beautiful woman and then
AI do the rest
Hey, what's up Nick Nick, would you have sex with her?
What do you think? Would you have sex with her or like?
No
If it was like a real if I was that would be the search that pretend it's on it like me as a
Transgender pretend it's like I was that's what I look like that's what I want to know not like because I'm not a transgender
Not yet anyway, I'm just gonna know I'm not playing on
Fuck now. I'm winning coffee, but I can't like really leave me. I can try to do IRL like walk to them McDonald's, but
Like nobody talking. I'm like, no, I shouldn't have started this
What am I thinking? Fuck I need coffee now. I really do and it's
Let's go
We can order it
Girl
Well, I'm gonna walk. I'm gonna walk hold on. I just need to hear give me a few minutes
Hold on just give me like I'm gonna put on this. Oh, I'm gonna put on a I
Made a few videos
see
Here oh
Here I made I made a few videos here. Here's one
Taste the biscuit
Damn
Okay, hold on a second, this one right here.
I don't see anything on the screen.
Oh my god.
Memento.
Anything? I just...
To teach is me not to break
My goddess and my shield, Scorpio's empire rising
My destiny
Got my stuff alone. I'm gonna try to go with kind of I'm a big breakfast. Okay. I'm freaking starving. Okay, so
Hey
Okay, I can go get cigars to
counter
It's order
Okay, yo, Tony. What's up?
Okay, so let me change out my thing and then I'm looking go for a walk. We'll do IRL this morning. How about that?
Cash me outside. How about that? That's like the IRL kind of like
Thing I don't know. So I'll see if I can get this going. Let's see
Streamy our
So, but yeah, tell me James's show is pretty decent. I'm think I thank him for having me on he was
I went to Kate's, and then he was kind of like,
oh, Psyche, he's like, oh, look at this guy in the chat.
He's like, I don't know if he always liked me that much,
but he was banned or something,
because I don't know, he'd probably piss me off
or something like that sometime.
Oh, he wasn't banned, like he did at one time he was,
but then I'm banned him like months ago,
but then I was in his chat and stuff, and then,
wouldn't even have seen it but somebody I don't know if they want me to tell
because I have like little secret sources that tell me stuff. I won't tell
who it was but someone sent me his link I thought it was scum's chat and I went
over there and it's like okay well and then I go in and like people were being
you know horrible in the chat and stuff and saying terrible things but he was
cool and Sig was there and Sig was like you know Sig I mean
SIG said he was snoring cocaine or something and he was
Think it's just SIG SIG hasn't been to my show for a while. I think he finally got tired of trying. I
Got tired of but yeah, he never would change. He just like it's hard
Kind of hard
When you're monetized and someone's trying to say the n-word and then they
Type of person that wants to go report himself for saying it like I hate that shit. So it's like I just
Didn't I just gave up finally, but Tommy kept having him on but I was like Tommy
He's not gonna stop. He's just he always
It's just gonna be like he's not gonna ever change. You can't like train
Some people you can train to like behave on the panel. No, not him
Never he's not ever gonna like listen. It's just gonna do it at the opposite of what you asked
Right in the right studio. No, I'm in the wrong studio shit and so I give up on sick, but
He was okay on the is okay
He wasn't really talking because he said he was doing coke and he was like so quiet
Like I've never seen him so quiet
But I don't know if he was doing coke, but
It was a
Mm-hmm. Hey Trixie. Yeah, we can go for a little IRL. Come on guys, we're new IRL
in a minute. You just have to give me a second because I'm a little bit slow right now.
Hold on. Okay, so there it is. Okay. Okay, there it is. Okay. Where's my email? Oh, there it is. Okay.
Yeah, I mean I have to go right now because my breakfast is almost ready, and I have to go to the store too. Yeah, so there we go
interest to you
Okay, let's go guys
You give a big breakfast then I'm probably gonna copy the report mostly but
Okay
That will be it'll be a vertical stream my death
PSY
Tricks just won't make
No, baby doll
Can I please enter the student? Oh
Guys, there's a really cute guy on the snapchat. It's like right. I mean
Can you see me?
Just one.
Oh, here I am.
Is this a vertical stream?
What is this called?
Vertical stream?
Is my sound okay?
Okay.
There's my fertilizer.
Now it's all wet, so I don't want to pick it up now.
Okay, guys, we're going on a big, big dive.
I guess I'll do vertical streaming.
Okay, here we go.
Beautiful little neighborhood.
I think I ran out of things thought I think I was on so many like hours long. I was on like
I was on
Used to be on for so long like 12 hours a day that I like told every like single story and like everything
I've already said and so even though nobody's they probably heard it. I
Feel like I've already said everything and so
Yeah, this guy's writing this guy's sending me these sexy
Video and he's I think he's straight. I don't know but then he was like, oh, do you want to like well
One guy was like he wanted me to he was saying I'll fly out but then I
Don't know I might trust
Okay
Here's my little walk every day
Feels kind of far. Oh, yeah breath shouldn't be smoking on the way
Yeah, I should go to the store first too, because I don't want to carry the breakfast.
Oh my god, how am I going to carry all this stuff?
Oh my god, it's like two coffees and I need a big breakfast in the phone.
I don't really think things ahead of time.
Hi, straight guys don't do that.
Well, but I give him, maybe he's not like totally straight though, you know.
But he's very present. He was like dancing and is like
Like these like basketball shorts like with a shirt off. He has all these really cool tattoos. He's really hot and
It's on snapchat. And so I don't know it's just some random
But he say but then he's like, you know
I put like fire emoji and then he starts sending me all these pictures all the time or these videos and he's like wrapping
He's a white guy wrapping. It's kind of funny
There's like actually there's a couple guys
But one of them one of the guys was like, oh, are you like he wants me like they're you're just interested in private content or something?
So I guess someone we're just trying to stuff
They guess smart if a guy's like not that
Well, but I think I was saying I don't troll on YouTube, especially anymore I
Used to but then it's like I think it's bad karma to do it on YouTube from first for me
Plus I'm like too kind of known
All right, but I used to just troll like a few people like Miss Netta and like stuff
But I don't use alts says
Christine was like accusing me of
Being HIV awakens tarot. I mean now I just be like I
When I do something that's that stupid. I mean it's like
Plus you've seen HIV awakens tarot in like other chats at the same time. Oh, oh, it's a somebody to drop some sauce
but uh
I'm out of breath. This is a library. Yeah, and so um, I
Don't know. Um, I think a guy can like, you know
Okay, we'll tell the story so on tick-tock
In this I would I like going on tick-tock because there's a lot of hot guys all right and so
Go on tick-tock and but I kind of like
Like I really like it inappropriate, right?
But then I got I get all the chat to start like being so so basically
They were like dancing around it was a black guy and a white guy the black guy was kind of heavy set
And black I didn't have a sure they were both like one wasn't a white beater one was had the black guy had a shirt off
And then they figured out I was a guy, right?
And they're like, what?
And then I start being really inappropriate.
Like, I always say, when there's a couple guys, I was like,
I want both of you at the same time.
And then they were like, all of a sudden, they're like,
expression change.
And they're like, what?
They're like, are you a guy or a girl?
And I'm like, I'm a beautiful woman, but then they look at my profile.
They can tell.
Okay, anyway.
But then I get the girls in there to start trolling them and then there's like other guys
I don't know it just turns and then everyone for them people were me then we were making like gay jokes and stuff like that and
They're like oh and then black I got so mad
But then I started like tipping them like a lot of flowers and stuff
Are like, you know rose and that's money on tiktok. It's like
It was not that's not like that much money. I tip like a but at first I put like a hundred roses, which is like a dollar, right?
And so they weren't really wanting to like get me out.
Okay, I'm on the street now.
It's not that far, huh?
And it was funny, but I got,
then it's like, and then it's like we got up to like,
they eventually like put their,
they both had their shirts off and were dancing.
And then it's like, they like got really uncomfortable.
They put back on their shirts and it was so funny.
And then I got all the girls' clothes.
I don't know, but you'd be impressed with me
People don't think I can but I can
especially on TikTok
Hey, what's up? Halo no introduction
Hey devil eyes either gay or trying to be I
Don't know. I think it's like there's a lot of guys that are oh shit
I just had a leaf in my face. There's a lot of guys that are gay for like gay for gay for pay
Well, I don't know especially nowadays
It's like
Like guys really don't care like like most of them don't even care that I that guys are hitting on them
And there's a lot of gay guys on tiktok hitting on them, and there's like, you know, I don't know some do I've only had one
Guy really like well, sometimes I'm like a little bit of a bitch and I like just we'll like
Join the fan club and then like leave real quick before I see the reaction
But if I say like most of the time they say thank you they do like I'll make you like put hands on hearts
I mean, it's like I don't know how they're like they all they pretty much figure out. I'm a guy
I don't know if this by my name or whatever because that my name is psyche is actually a female name his name of a
Goddess if I haven't told you a million times, okay, but
And then I have a pic I just have a picture I have on my profile is just like a graphic
It's like a graphic of a monster or something, but I don't know they figure out
If they go to my page, they can see.
Okay, I'm at the liquor store.
Oh my God.
Okay, I need to put out my cigar.
Grab a couple more.
One.
This is IRL, but it's not the best IRL, I'm sorry.
Hi.
You're welcome.
You too, sweetie.
I appreciate you.
Have a good weekend.
Hi. Can I get the rest of the Dutch? Yeah, thank you.
So, I might need, thank you so much.
Have a good day. Bye. Bye. I might see LD tonight. I don't know if it will work out, but that'd be cool. He's in town
We were like last night. He was on with this girl. She had peak here guys. It was so hilarious last night
Oh my god, but Mason. Oh my god. Do you see Goddy and Mason last night? Oh, yeah
Mason and Goddy was really funny
Oh, there he is, just got he just right into writing the chat what Mason said to you and I had to end the stream
If you can write in the chat, I can't say I'm grabbing McDonald's
I got the big breakfast of McDonald's and a couple of coffees and I got I just bought cigars
If you he's not in Philadelphia. He's an LA right now. He's like in Long Beach, which is oh
Yeah, he's a long beach, which is like basically 10 15 minutes away. It's a really close and so
Yeah
He says, he's, we're gonna go to a, I need to fix my,
fix my cell phones again.
He's either gonna go, he said either like a bar,
which is nearby or like a graveyard.
That'd be fun.
I'd love to do that, but you know,
I don't know if it'll work out,
but it's hard for me to go.
I don't even have my bike right now.
Still not repaired.
It's stuck in my garage. It's in my garage right now with the fucking. I told you what happened to the bike
It's really embarrassing. I don't really like talking about it, but I
Was right. I got the fucking lock stuck on it
And then I forgot if the lock was on and I started writing it and then the lock got like all
Granted inside the gears like some part of it like and then now so now and I can't open the lock anymore
so I need to get like
like a
huge thing of like
Cutters, you know
Yeah, yeah
It was funny you got Basin got so mad
His body was just kind of messing with him. He wasn't even messing with him that hard. It was just like
But Mason is very, he was very triggered.
I love Mason, amazing.
But yeah, it's not triggered, he's like,
so I'm gonna beat you up.
And I took the part where he said beat you up,
but then like there was like a, you know,
AI makes clips on StreamYard, it makes them little shorts.
And it had, it put in the THROATCOTTINB part.
Like it put in like the, or he said that part.
I wanted to share it, but I can't.
You know, it's like a little bit.
I don't think it's good for YouTube, right
So okay here I'm at McDonald's
This is gonna be a fun walk
Hey look
Here we go
Okay
This is mine
Hello
Can I get on the carrier, please? Yes. Thank you so much
It was funny. It was it was very scary. Thank you so much
Yeah, thank you so
Okay, success
Now I just gotta walk home
okay luckily my dad like picked out this place especially for like because he
knew like I wasn't driving at the time I haven't driven since like 2018 when my
car basically melted on the freeway I had a Mercedes SUV it was pretty nice but
uh yeah that it melted okay my pants are kind of falling down okay anyway
Hey Alexandra
Yeah, I'm getting some solid IRL. I got the McDonald's walk. Here's the library. There's a Starbucks
I have I don't go to Starbucks anymore because I can get basically free coffee
at the bagel place
But McDonald's I get basically free coffee too because I did the app
You can get it for like a dollar fifty instead of like four dollars pretty good deal
But at the bagel place
I basically just keep a cup and I can go anytime like and just go in and fill it and they don't
they've never care. It's unlimited. They just throw away the coffee anyway. You know, it's like,
it's not like it's like that great of a coffee. But uh, yeah, I do that sometimes. I can do that
until like 130. They close at 130. I'm already halfway home. This is pretty fast, huh? I'm a
fast walker. Alexandra knows she was, she saw me walking, right? We walk together.
okay there's a lot of people at this library right now okay here this is
where oh what's going on here oh I know what it is okay it's like the special
special group here we go
so I'm gonna walk home as fast as I can
Yes, oh, thank you. Yeah, they film Baywatch here. Oh, it's one's calling
What you for I don't know. I got all know all these like I'm
Telephone list somehow, but anyway, yeah, yeah, we had a nice little walk up the street
But yeah, and then the peers a few blocks down that way you can see here's like the
This is like the Whole Foods. There's a Michaels
There's the down that way is the beach. I'm sorry
I need to work I need to get like a selfie stick and stuff. I have one block to go
Okay
and
Yeah, I am as much fun though
Alexandra and hopefully like maybe I'll see LD today who knows
It's like I guess I would just have to meet them pretty close by
They're pretty close. I would love to, but uh, yeah, we'll see. Okay. Yeah. So you guys saw the manure
in front of my house last night. We also, I also had, I had about three or four people come to the door
and it's like, really, I, at this point, I don't even care. It's just like, it's not even annoying
They're usually pretty nice. Oh shit, the sprinklers just run. They're usually pretty nice
But it's like the amount of like waste is that is being accumulated with the fucking
They're like mom-and-pop shop pizza places that are the ones that deliver
Pray
And they order like like two pizzas or stuff. The people look so they piss off
But I just tell them I'm like just just
Call the person back and yell at them or something, you know
Or report the number to the police. I was like they're they're scamming. I was like, but I have the manure in front of the door
So I can say look
They're they're sending me manure and they go, oh, let me just turn around right away
They're nice people usually it's of course not their fault
But it's like he's really pranking them and it's like that there are like
Innocent bystanders. It really sucks
I mean, it's like
this ridiculous that
People are doing that stuff. Okay. Okay
Okay, I'm already home by the way I
Docs myself a long time ago like because uh, I
You know said I've already said my name my city. I think they figured out. I don't know. I don't know. Oh, yeah, it was because uh, I
They had it beg this guy. I like he was a spy in our discord and so
There's some stuff shared in the private chat that like you know got shared and stuff and so but everyone was Doc's
Janet Bita and myself all at once
You know by who he's a dick you mean he's he admits it on the air and stuff
Which is like not that smart I think to do
Yeah, there's a manure by the way
But it's the nice kind right it's like a
Weed free and fine screen that means it has no no weed in the cow shit, right?
Well, it's not that great of weather, huh? Okay, I'm home so I can turn on my other camera. I'll be right back
Okay
You're right back
Like I'm exercised for the day. Oh, I have to get my phone
Hi Trixie
Thanks
Y'all really sitting here tricks, okay, I made some videos
I did a rigid capricorn rising. Oh, if you're here Alexander, I think you like the original one
I made I made a new one. I'm experimenting with like different music styles
That's the thing you can there's like quite 50 music styles to choose from and you can like
Choose multiple ones, right? They can blend them and
so
It really is like
Interesting like trying like because I'm learning more about the musical style like somebody didn't really understand
So it's like the more I do like and I'm listening back to some of my old songs
I'm like, oh that they kind of some of them are not very good compared to like my newer stuff
So you can see my news. This is a new song. Yeah, hold on. Whoo
Capricorn rising. I'm very hot right now. Here we go
Voice of the dawn, where the climb's begun
Words like pillars, fire in my hands
I build a temple, long shifting sands
Capricorn rising, storm in my eyes
Aquarius moonlight, thunder cracks the sky
A gente viu!
Visions made flesh, I declare it now.
Autumn leaf and the gavel fall.
Through death and dawn, I will guide them on.
Rebel stars in the tribal flame.
Dreams cross borders, none stay the same.
I love that. I love that. I really do love the tricks one better. The problem was like it uh
I'm still figuring out how to how to re-edit it because maybe like on the editor other engine
it just does like four minutes and then it cuts off abruptly. I don't know why it does that but
this new engine it does the songs longer and stuff but uh yeah there's a newer one.
Oh thank you guys thank you so much um yeah I'll show you my breakfast.
Um, I mean tricks it might eat half my bacon. They didn't really they go really really young here have some sausage here
Have some sausage
here
This cat look sausage tricks here
Yeah, what's the sausage here?
And Lola do you want it?
It's McDonald's McDonald's sausage eat it yummy
I put it down. He'll eat it here. There you go. You're gonna eat it. Maybe he's eating it now
Oh, just drop it here
Go ahead eat it you like it up like McDonald's
And then a no pancakes he wants the butter here eat that here a little bit over here here eat it
Okay
You want some a little here you have a piece too. Yeah, I need to share my sausage with the cat
Mmm, this is good, really good.
Trix always likes to knock over my softish, you know?
And the Nordus do sometimes.
I scream, oh, they're eating it.
Lola, eat some, Trix is getting it all.
Lola, eat some.
She's not aggressive, you like him.
There it is, they're eating it.
Hmm
He wants what he wants whatever I'm eating. Oh, look at Rudy home. Look at Rudy. He's so cool
Hey Rudy
Hey, Rudy
The little man cat. What are you doing? He's been looking up the catnip on the thing. It was like, oh my god
There's catnip everywhere. Yes, it's catnip what you can just brush it off
You're so silly you like sitting on that cabinet cat in a pillow. Yeah
The cutie
Yeah, you didn't run over for the food
He's such an old man. You're like a little old man
When I see him when I see him Lola go over to say how to Rudy
Thank you, isn't he a beautiful cat, huh? Yeah, you're sleepy
Sleepy rude. Hi rude boy
It's beautiful. I love his like beautiful. He has these beautiful yellow eyes. Hi, what do you do?
And we queue up
Morning time, bro, buddy. Hey buddy. Oh, hey buddy boy. Oh
Here I come over the root
Okay
Just here with the cats. Oh always crazy. Here. Here. Here. Lola you eat that you eat that you can have this awesome
Hey, hey, you eat top eating my pancake. He's licking the butter off my pancake. Hey tricks
You're licking the butter off my pancake and look guys guess what I got I got a
Bits get now I think it's English muffin, right?
and pancakes and stuff and then you put surf all over it.
They are cute. And there's Lola. Lola.
My table's not that bad today. Hey, Lola. Want to say hi?
There, I'm going to pick you up.
She's like, dad, no.
What about you?
Can I pick you up?
Oh, Trixie, oh, Trixie, oh.
Go down.
Okay.
Yeah, so I did make a few of the videos today of this morning,
so I thought I would give me three or four.
But I was, you know, I just wanted to show a few of those.
Did everyone see the picture of me as a woman and Arthur already said oh that doesn't look like I mean
It doesn't really I mean, it's it would be if I looked like this. I would love that right, but I mean if I was a woman, right, but
How do I look
Pretty good
I kind of like almost like Alyssa Giordano, like a little like Alyssa Giordano like a little bit.
Oh, you saw it. Okay, good.
Yeah.
Yeah, I did look like that. I didn't, when I was like, let me see.
I think it's eighth grade. Yeah, I think it was eighth grade. Well, in sixth grade, I was Norman Bates's mother for Halloween, right?
So I was like this grandma.
Triangle in the Sun. Oh the actors from the Gilmore Girls. Yeah
I was like thinking like actually I know this girl named Shana
She's like a friend of mine, and it kind of like her. I'll see if I can find her picture. She's on Facebook. Let me see and
It looks kind of like her a little bit, let me see yeah, I can't find her
Yeah
Well
Oh, hold on, I need to pick up the screen, hold on.
Take that off.
That's Shawna.
Hey, hey, hey, kept her fighting.
Actually, it looks like mine is the beer Christy Turlington.
Yeah, well, I mean, I did cheat a little bit.
I said, make me look like a beautiful woman.
And so it probably, you know, maybe look a little bit better,
I might look when I did drag when I was like the eighth grade
My mom is like extra small right and she's really good style, but she has this big bag with the clothes she would give away
But went and I stole like this her like a blonde albira week. She had
And then get extra small dress out of her leg out of her charity bag
And I came down and dragged my it was like an opposite day or cross-dressing there or something
I was like basically the only guy that did it
and
My parents laughed
Yeah, that was that was funny. I don't think it's so funny now, but I
Look pretty good. I do have pictures of it. So I can find them so I
Showed before
Yeah
I'm happy
Let's share with them here
Yeah, yeah
Go and play
We like the pancake
The pancake here it's both you like you just like the syrup I think here. I'm syrup alone. Here you go
There you go. Try that
Just sugar. It's plain sugar. You'll love it
Look
Do you want this he just wants to eat it from my plate? Why don't you want to eat your own plate? No, no, no, no, right there
baby right there
Silly kitty cat. They don't eat human meat
What do you mean like humans about a lion would eat me baby, right?
they they meet the cat my cats eat everything um what i'm trying to think about the weirdest
stuff my cats eat but there's a lot of stuff cats can't eat so you have to like look at a list of
stuff because there's stuff that's not very good for them right it's not human come on gaudy it's
not human i think they did find like maybe like one percent dn of human dna in the in the meat i
Mm-hmm
I'm sorry if I'm like a little bit of a messed up you know, but
The way I eat is I get like really hungry and then I eat I
Think I was playing for the camera, but this ally guy has all these videos of me like stuffing food in my mouth and like
I was kind of being like, kind of like trying to be funny.
Remember when I tried to be funny
and then it looks kind of bad?
Yo, what's up, Mason?
How are you feeling today?
Oh, is that you backstage?
No, it's fine.
That's my, that's my female picture backstage still, okay.
Hey, Mason, how are you feeling today?
Hello, Key Man.
Hello, everybody.
I'm just, it's called like enjoying your food, right?
Of course, Mason.
how we got your back.
I will always have my friends back as much as I can.
And now there's been like, some people are mad
that I haven't spoken up at the right time.
And it's like, maybe, I loved,
did you see the Jerry Springer footage?
I'll play, I don't know if I can,
I can show that again, I can show that again, hold on.
It's just like a big the beginning of that video because it's like they put me on like Jerry Springer
And they put me on our trip kick that you know put me on Jerry Springer and he put me on
Like all the guests and then show the Springer show and stuff. I didn't know and then it's like, you know
It's pretty funny though, and let's see and I
Like this it's pretty cool
It's funny, okay here
Okay, sure
Okay, watch this
So that's me, right, okay
I say a damn thing when I'm in a hurry, so I'm gonna still do my damn thing
While I do my worst
My dad told me, he didn't see a hill, anything, said two times, god damn it, she worked
They can't keep up, won't keep up, I overdose
Won't wake up, she off the wall, on the adderah
She do perk, I said, like they Tylenar
All these drugs, get me by myself
Mama tell me they don't really killin' myself
She say I need help, I don't need help
No, I can do better by myself
If they ain't did it they won't
Just drop pussies
I'm not crying about AI song. It's other people that
Aggressive about it. I don't give a fuck. It's just like I'm going with the bullshit lies and like the rumors
And some of them are like really dark and sick. Like I definitely didn't harm my ex-husband
Not part of like any kind of mafia never even like
I'm
Like I pay every like my tickets my registration my I'm like every I'm like a very legal person
I've never been arrested for anything like hello
Call not getting caught right?
And you literally been here watching it like a fucking bitch though. I can do you a favor
You can just leave you don't have to watch me. You know, it's easy peasy
No, HK. It's not taking the joke seriously. It's a lot of other things that you don't see. It's about antagonizing and
like, you know, just bringing up stuff when you're trying to, you know, when you try to just let things summer, somebody pokes at you, pokes at you, pokes at you.
Do you remember when I would be on your show and we had Alexander NYPD
All these people attacking me calling me names. It would be like a bunch of people coming at me
What did I do defend my own fucking war, right?
Mm-hmm. I defend my war. I mean, I'm not like having so if people have like issues with like, you know
Certain things that you do and they're like, you know coming at you. What do you think about that?
Like why don't you just like accept it as a that's their opinion? Oh, I do. I do. I mean, it's like what I mean
But I was kind so that's what I think about it. It happened. I you know, you left the panel
And then what I think was that Christine was telling you that it does hurt her it's a sensitive subject for her as I can relate, you know, you know, like my ex husband and you know you thinking that's fucking bullshit like I'm had something to do with Aaron Carter and all these
Mm-hmm. Yeah, people people people. It's what you think so but it's what you allow
He knows all the fucking fucked up shit that J-Dog is done all this fucking shit
But you know other people
You know that person on purpose just to talk about me all day long, you know
I don't know respect for people that will bend over for
Doxers for disgusting like J-Dog that are criminals and you know see this is that you nodding your hair blah blah blah blah
you'd want to do this you can go ahead and do it you know i mean you're literally like digging
yourself even more you're not here to communicate you're not here to listen go make you you're
actually here for attention you will never take responsibility and that's the way it goes i don't
want a fake friendship i don't want a fake friendship so basically a friend's rider like you
listen
I'm not a fucking fence rider, I'm just literally doing my life.
People are coming here and they're going, I'm not inviting any of you guys.
Like, here you come here, whatever, this and that.
I'm getting trolled.
You already came here like 70 times and you left.
Like, what the fuck am I fucking fence riding?
Like I'm not in the mood like you're like, you know what it is. Maybe you're like
And you know what you don't have to you can leave
You came up here. You went out like the first guess the second guess the third guess now you're bored and you're
I'm gone after anybody really I saw trying to tell jokes with people
I don't remember Spaz. I'm the commas person.
You've been spazzing out all night.
This guy pulled out his dick on my stream three times.
Be very careful.
He doesn't point bomb, but he does.
He's pointing bomb on me.
Just wait for it.
I've been perfectly calm.
You crashed out hard.
I'm the commas person.
You're going to get clipped.
I'm gonna get a club for being called.
The Times Outreach.
I probably duo you with some apologies,
Bita, for like, you know, for everything, you know,
for not like...
Sticking up for you, like you know, like maybe not for being the best friend and
You don't have to be a best friend and you don't have to stick up for me
You just gotta you know not entertain the bullshit when it's sensitive things like when it comes down to you know
People like you know, like just take me or Christine for example. We told you several times, you know, you're talking about
People that are not either here or for her. This is like, you know, she's kind of an activist even if she does
She's a nurse. So it's like she's a supporter of yours. We are, you know, women
It's like kind of sensitive like why go and make a title about it, you know, that's it like because she was saying
Oh, well, I wasn't I wasn't doing what you're saying. I was doing and I was like, yeah, you were on
Share with crystal and you were laughing at what she was saying because nobody thinks crystal really seriously when she goes off on people because she makes
Everybody literally she says I'm a bad person. I'm evil
No, but but some of the stuff that crystal was saying wasn't even it was like she was talking about her
Offing children, you know, um, that's how funny it was bad, but it was like so ridiculous
But it is like there's a line where it's not funny where you're like listen, that's I'm not gonna
I'm gonna put you backstage. You're not gonna be talking about somebody like that. That's disgusting
You're not gonna entertain it and egg it on and be like and what else and tell me more
once you make a mistake like that and you are told several times by her and summer and other people this bothers me you just double down triple down like I don't know you keep doing it over and over sorry the times you keep interrupting so I have to play you know for can put you backstage all right when you see somebody like a J dog making up rumors and gossip about me and somebody like Alexander mayors that goes on and does concert like consp...
everything you mod everybody over there and you let it go on and hold on I'm
talking now you let it go on and on and you're like it's not a big deal it's a
joke you know you're actually hurting people by just like co-signing with it
so you're siding with me I thought you're trying to come against me well you
interrupt so much that good times you like to hear yourself just talk
I believe people should be free to do whatever.
All right, we got it, we got it.
We know, we got it.
Longest to not hurting other people, right?
Yeah, exactly.
And as long as that you're not like spreading false narratives
about other people and laughing and joking about it.
Because some things that it could be,
it's almost antagonizing.
It's like poking.
You know and then you're poking at people's emotions and it sucks. It's not really cool y'all make a lot of judgments and sometimes we
Would you let psyche speak God you love good time do it again in truck
No, he was responding sorry I react based on being
Myself being triggers and I have triggers right and it's like a community know how to push buttons and stuff and so
a lot of times I'm just reacting instead of like
Acting right and so it's like I do have to have a lot of stuff to work on myself
And it's like people like you like help you know bring awareness to myself. And so ultimately no matter how
Mad or anybody isn't me. It's like it does help. It's helped me to understand things now. Not the most
socially advanced person right and so back you know the Christine thing I do
regret because she never did anything wrong to me like I mean so I wasn't it
wasn't like oh I'm gonna go try to slander Christine I'm gonna do this or
that right it's like I was just like caught up in the moment and I was like oh
this is kind of
She's saying ridiculous things, you know, she's oh, she's on her medicine again or something or offer medicine
Well, I don't know whatever. What do you know like listen
Then you did it again, and then you went and like made a title about it
We're talking yesterday about like I was like well
Christine you were on with crystal and crystal was saying this up and you were just laughing about it
And so I thought you kind of had like this understanding of
Crystal, Christine wasn't in that conversation. Maybe when they were laughing, it wasn't that
weird of a subject that what Crystal was talking about. It was a whole different way of a different
level. Okay. So I mean, it wasn't about her saying, Crystal, you know, Christine, you
know, her children, which is very, like she actually helps children. So she wasn't there
could have just been like, hey, let's not talk about Christine, move on,
let her talk about blah, blah, blah, something else, Crystal.
But then let's forget that.
That was a mistake that happened.
But then you clipped it and then you did it again.
And then you folks out again and then again.
But I was saying to hold on to Christine.
Yeah, I was like I was saying the whole time to crystal. I was like Christine if you're here get up here right now
I was like, I want to hear I was like, no that doesn't sound like Christine that I know I know
I was saying like people were saying I agree with her. I didn't agree with her one time
You can watch the clip. I was saying no, no, no crystal. I was like no, but I was a bit sometimes I was acting like
You're talking about Christina. We know like I was like I was eating so I was being green watch
sarcastic or like a little bit like you know the ceaseless or whatever, but
Maybe it seemed like I was agreeing with her or endorsing her.
I do not anyway.
Christine's a wonderful, wonderful, I respect nurses so much and so I have affection for
nurses and I have a lot of nurses and medical people on my show.
You have people in your chat that say that I oft my husband, both of my exes, I don't
know, somebody named Jar Jar, I have things done with my animals, you know, listen.
No, you just like, you just love to come on live and act like, well,
Bita's mad at me.
Bita said this and that, because I got messages from you saying, Bita,
you know what, I'm sorry, you know, I'm going to just lay off.
You do your thing.
I said, you too.
love you, love you too. And what do you do? Go back again and play. Listen, let me tell you
something. Maybe the woman that you dealt with in your life before, they might have had dried
biscuit, but my shit is fucking juicy. There's a reason why there's a, you know, there's a virgin
fucking spell. All right. And I'm not fucking menopausal.
So stop telling people since I turned 50, you don't know what happened like a few months
in my life.
I did have somebody very close to me pass away.
No, I did not have anything to do with that.
If you are a real friend and checked in once in a while and called and talked to like as
a human being instead of going there and coming up with your own assumptions.
I don't know. There's a lot of mutual people that don't like either one of them.
Her name is Kate, right? Okay, so that's what my name is Kate.
I don't think this has anything to do with Kate at all.
Let me finish. I was going to say, Kate, be plain.
your show like what I came on and everything and even Kate he was like
oh look at where to see fucking psyche embarrass himself she was like wow
she's like I had beta like yelling at me like that and then Bronzeberg yelling at
me she's like I would have been a bitch too you know it's like
I got empathy from her because she's like, wow.
Really, I watched that back.
It was, I was not close enough to my microphone,
I don't think, and I was kind of quiet.
Did you have empathy when Alexander McQueen
and all these people are yelling at me,
J-Dog is accusing me of stuff like that?
Or when you have Alexander,
me are sitting up there bringing up
my personal relationships, my family.
Did you think that for a second other people that you've done the same thing to on the panel don't have a right to be upset and go at you or what you said about
bronze bird you sit there and you make fun of him you're like telling him oh you're below me because you have less subscribers or blah blah blah blah
or like you know
What was he saying to me be that what was he saying to me
Well what the fuck he used to be a supporter of yours here maybe you guys can talk
Oh god you period all this stuff
Oh god no
I'm right here, if you guys sign in and say to me we can talk about it bro.
I will, you're a fucking bronze chicken.
See?
Okay that's corny, but if you guys sign in and say to me you can talk to me.
I will, I don't have anything to say to you bronze chicken.
You can have a conversation. You're being naughty already. You're being naughty. He hasn't said nothing. He just came up here and he said, can we have a conversation?
Let's discuss this. Let's discuss this. You're not real. You're fake and you know that. I don't understand why you can't be real and you can't tell Bita why you was making A.I. diss songs towards her.
No, you was not being playful. You was in your feelings and you was making AI diss songs towards Vita because Vita was
Exposing to real you and you didn't like
Just like every single time you come on a panel
You want to shut the fuck up while I'm talking or you still want to run your mouth?
Oh, wow, you were talking over me the entire time
Dirty ass motherfucker
Like no, I told you right
So why would you make an AI diss songs towards beta?
Why would you get in all upset when you got kicked off of summer's panel?
To speak for me he joined right now and he has his issues with psyche and you know
Maybe they can resolve it. No, it's not no resolve in anything.
I have a lot of things. I'm like, trust me.
You can talk about me not being on camera.
It doesn't make a difference. It doesn't make a difference.
I'm not on camera either. And neither is possible.
You don't give a shit about your community. You only give a shit about your channel.
That's what you give a fuck about. You backstab your friends and then everybody calls you out
and make a stream about it then you talk shit about my channel as a way to sit up there and
scapegoat to sit up there have something to say about me I don't think we'll fuck if you ever come
to my streams you know why there's only real people coming to my streams not fake motherfuckers like
you that sit up there and want to talk about your channel all day on tiktok all right you guys can you
Listen, listen, I tried to be cordial with the scumbag
But no, I used to come to your channel you guys is to be fuck psyche. Yo, I can't stand fake motherfuckers like psyche
Yo, okay, sit up there. Why are you when he doesn't want it? He when he doesn't he has his opinion
Why is that upset you so much? You always know how bronze bird was he's gonna be stern about his beliefs and what he thinks
Like me so he's gonna like, you know, say, oh, you're done motherfucking
You are
You proved it yourself. You shit it on your friends when it came to your streams.
When people try to support you dumbass you sat there and went over to Emma and fucking
Jordana, bro
I don't give a fuck bro. That's what you did every single time it came to your channel. You shit it on your own friends
That's why I call you fake you dumb fuck
Psyche your fake you don't have a community you go to you shit on your friends and every time you want to come on your stream
It's about oh, I went on tic-tac and I got 70,000 views and blah blah blah. I have more views than you Rob's bird
Like I said, why do you think you're better than me because you have a thousand more subs than me?
Why do you think you're better than me?
I'm just gonna interrupt you.
Oh, bruh, it's better than me!
Answer the question.
What's the question?
Why do you think you're better than me because you have one thousand more subs than me?
I don't think I'm better than you.
You say it all the time.
You want to make fun of my fucking channel and shit.
I don't take it personally, but you'd love to make it a reference, you know how Psyche likes to run away from his problems?
He doesn't like to confront a real man. He doesn't like to confront a real man. That's why he likes to go for little jugglers and dumb shit.
I'm right here, okay. Go ahead.
You was talking shit about my channel. You was talking shit about my channel, but you needed people to make your channel high.
That's the problem. That's the thing you don't understand.
That's why I'm better than you and I'm more real than you ever be in your life.
I'm better than you.
You're real.
And you mad.
Brooklyn streets.
I'm broke what?
Just hear that.
Let's not talk about this, bro.
I said Brooklyn.
Did you guys hear that?
And then then he say I said broke, right?
And they still are saying I called him broke or something like that.
But I said Brooklyn very clearly.
Right, because I said you just have a picture of the Brooklyn streets or something like that in this picture
I don't know where it is, but I said Brooklyn Street, whatever, right? I don't know
That conversation because you asked me for money you asked me for money psyche don't start talking shit about
Don't do that because you sitting in your house being dirty as fuck bro
Don't do that. Don't do that with your dirty ass nails and your dirty ass couch. Don't do that
You don't want to talk about broke, bro
I will, I will drag the fuck out of you about you from this.
I'm afraid of you, bronze, but a little-
You mad dirty.
You sit up there and cry about how your nails is dirty on strings
since everybody talked about how dirty you are.
You're dirty, you're not clean, you don't shower.
You sit on your cat's shit, piss, fucking couch and shit.
the fuck out of here don't you ever talk about my financial situation right now psyche and then don't
get mad when he's giving a back to you you just said he's broken he fucking don't know you don't
know shit about my financial situation you asked me for money remember that psyche the fuck out of
here you would sit up there and you would sit up there stripping for fucking trolls and get your
channel back for nine dollars let's talk about that shit i never had to do that shit even if i
Let's talk about that shit. You fucking cloud chaser. Everybody know you a fucking cloud chaser psyche
That's why I call you fake. You shit on your friends. You shit it on beta
You shit it on Tracy. You shit it on Christine. You shit it on flirty diamond
You shit it on every single person that came in a fucking panel fake fuck
Fuck you
Want to sit up there and talk about my financial situation bitch? I wish you would
really
Everybody's entitled to their opinion including you Samantha Avery, but you're not noticing how psyche is sitting there
I don't know taking your responsibility putting down another man. Let's don't forget some of the racist shit
That we're not gonna go back and talk about that he allowed like you know me
Like he allowed you to sit up there and talk down on me.
You don't know.
Just get in the car and go back and forth some after Avery.
I mean, I've given you enough respect
to just tell you you have your own opinion too, OK?
Things don't go well on my panel.
Psyche takes it out on me, not other people.
He takes it out on me.
Don't be passive aggressive.
Bumper is like making good points.
And like, you know, you're just like fishing out.
If you do your hand or shit.
You don't want him to get upset.
You're coming in for but I don't see Brunsberg fucking saying he needs money to host a panel or like that.
Thank you. I'm not asking people for ten dollars to join a panel. You are, psyche.
What the fuck are you talking about?
You know what, you know how low my live stream was? I had only five viewers in my stream.
They still had my shit down for four hours. So you want to talk shit? Talk shit, bro.
You know what, I'll never be, I'll never be a money hungry motherfucker like you that sit up there telling people to come up with a stream for ten dollars.
That's what you do.
And I make the ten dollars, don't I?
Aw, bitch, yeah.
So, what are you gonna complain about?
Because you need it, you desperate bitch.
If you don't wanna be on these panels,
get the fuck off of YouTube and go to TikTok.
You get your 70,000 viewers.
You wanna get monetized so bad.
Hey, motherfucker, you wanna sit out there and go to IP2
and you can handle motherfuckers that was on your panel.
Let us speak.
fuck psyche you fake fuck don't you think he wants to get monetized like i think it's not a competition
psyche that's where you are always thinking competitively you message me you're like yeah
you have this many people watching you or this beat i'm like i told you psyche it doesn't matter
none of that fucking shit matter there's like times where i'm off and you're going to get a
lot of fucking viewers it just depends on who's live who's on the panel it's just a lot of different
Oh
Wow, yeah, like you could couldn't you hear me very clearly like I
Mean, it's my fault. I mean if I can say one thing about Bronzeberg. He does have a quality
He was you know, but I do have a much better microphone now and I need to put it closer to me
This is I mean wow
I mean, it's just like shocking to me like, you know, and it's like and then she's like, oh, oh poor Bronzebird. I mean, it's like
Geez
Anyway
Mason are you behaving in the are you behaving in the chat Mason?
What's going on between remember the song called the beautiful people. Yeah beautiful people
That was a good song. I've seen Marilyn Manson several times in a concert. I've actually met him, too
But I don't need to talk like this the microphone when I'm talking to people
Hey, what's up Queen Natalie, how are you? I'm sorry. I didn't mean to talk to them. I mean
Geez Louise guys, I mean did you hear I didn't hear one word. I said he's just talking over me like a
You know
You're bronze chicken. I don't know. I'm sorry. I shouldn't even I
don't know why I
Find it entertaining though. I do find it a little bit entertaining that
I'm right
Six oh so easy
I need to talk like this all day talk like this all day
I mean, I don't want to fucking hurt people's ears. I mean jeez. I don't need to like scream like that
I mean if I could they have a chance to like yeah, and the Queen Natalie's here. What's up, Natty?
That he's awesome. I
Did some I did some good shorts from her appearance the other day
They're really good
talked about
Stuff I want to talk about on this show like interesting things like
Basically, I'm I think I'm really going in more the direction. I wanted to go down this stuff. It's like
Good riddance of this, I mean, it's like, you know a little is fine, but oh
I'm just like it gives me a headache. I'm sorry
You know, it's like I just need to watch some of this stuff. It's good to see yourself myself back
But you know what what I lacked in a
In my voice that day, I certainly made up for hand gestures. I certainly have the hand gestures going on, right?
I'm certainly expressive. I don't know if it's a gay thing or not
I remember now even when I was younger they used to say you use your hands a lot. Oh
Yeah, Paul though a little bark it's like a little attack dog like why do we need an attack dog?
You know and bring him right up. I mean
but uh
That's who she'd rather hang out with
Obviously she cares more about his feelings, you know
So ridiculous, I mean it's like
And like Alexander Meyers played a or did she had a great show yesterday and you can go see it on
IRL news time. I believe it's on the IRL news time channel, right or the ip2 wiki.info
And she was basically she had
She was she saw one of where I said
You know if you don't want to be talked about like and I you know, of course, you know
And I've learned this the hard way, maybe
But if you don't want to be talked about if you don't want to have your name out there
You don't want to be doxxed I
Would recommend just don't go on panels don't go on YouTube don't host a show
This is like, you know, just Oprah get to not compare myself to Oprah, of course, right?
But his Oprah get to like, you know
Say oh, you know, you know, I don't want my last name out there. What I mean, it's like
It's also if you're gonna be in the public eye, and I know this is not like made
I'm not like any kind of major celebrity. I'm not even like a d-list
I mean, I'm not I'm like, you know a very tiny like little blip in the radar of any kind of
any kind of like, you know anything but
Still I understand
I'm going if I'm gonna have like a million views eventually I will I have probably about half a million views already
But I'm gonna you know get have millions of people watching
eventually, right
That's putting myself out there right and so why have a show also yeah, also
But the problem. Oh, you like Christine. I have a problem with it. I don't have a problem with Christine. Christine has a problem with me
She came and
No, I can just let you see how she talked to me. I mean, I don't know if you've seen the Scotty like uh, yeah, she uh
She had
After the you know the crystal thing. I was very everyone's in the crystal thing. Yeah, she came and you know chewed me out or whatever
But it wasn't anything like
Was I allowed to apologize ever no was that I mean I've apologized several times. I don't accept your apology, you know
Some friend, right?
You're thinking, you know, friend, you know, might,
that was the first time I,
we ever had an issue and she decides to like,
you know, jump me over that, right?
Right?
Ooh, I'm almost wanting to play this black widow tape again.
But I don't wanna make things too crazy.
Let me see, so, oh, yeah, so this is, okay,
so let me see, where's the,
Where's the where I get my ass chewed out by Christine? Let's see
Takes the gloves off, but okay
By the way, I'm feeling really stupid
About yet and well, okay
People that are gonna lie about having cancer, I think that's disgusting
Okay, I think it's disgusting and I really I don't even know if I should bring it up, but
There is a woman, you know that I was having a lot of sympathy for right
Because she's going through health issues, all right
And I'm hearing that this this young woman
Was like
At the supermarket like I work out, you know, I don't I I don't know. I don't I shouldn't even
But if she yeah, it's I don't I don't have anybody's you know medical anything, right? I don't know but it's like what I'm hearing is that
She was lying about this to get donations like a $10 donation or something
That's true
That is fucking disgusting and it's like
Also have another problem with that person because I mentioned like oh well what happened with the Aaron Carter thing and she said
Oh, well, yeah, he was on drugs. So we you know, we basically trolled him to death
What the fuck is that? I'm like
What does it matter if someone's on drug like why is that a reason to troll them to death? That just seems like
Pretty fucking heartless, right? I don't know. I
really hope that I'm a
I'm wrong about it, but I just got some information that
basically I'm not wrong about it and
That really disturbs me
It's not any kind of like medical thing like lying about medical stuff. I mean, yeah
What did I it's like, you know fish tacos is one thing and it wasn't even like, you know
I see fish tacos. That's just that you can take a myth of taking his own own life of its own
But lying about cancer for ten dollars
Come on
That's pretty insane
Doesn't I'm talking about where's the crystal thing? Oh, yeah, Christine is not happy here. We go
When you're gonna see this guy here we go
Christine is not happy about something
Mine now
Christina are you there? Yes, I'm here. Christine. What is that about? Oh, let me tell you what that is about
How dare you how fucking dare you you don't see me going other channels talking shit about you
You have a delusional fucking
Staying next shit about me and then yours now. No, not our Christine and then oh, she's a nurse. Fuck you psych fuck you
Oh, no, no, no, no, no. You don't get to make excuses. I said he's had here and I've watched
Trevor bullshit. You've been doing and I've not said bullshit to you or about you and any of these other chats
You can go straight to hell and you keep your little drunks and your little druggies and your little
polls in your chat
because
People like me that have supported you for all these months will never support you again ever
Okay, well, why are you so mad? Why?
Wow, you know something you made yourself look dumb
Don't make excuses don't make excuses do not make excuses
You've been going after everybody saying they're threatening you they're saying bad things about you and you're a fucking drunk up here
talking about fagotry and Christine killed kids and and you said she said I
listen to it site you you can go to fagotry is talking about do you
understand me she's talking about the tree of us
I don't know that was like, you know, I was like letting Crystal look ridiculous because I thought she's a great night
I thought nobody like believed it, but it's like
Well, I can't I can't tell it comes out of her mouth, you know, I was like actually I was literally talk because it's a look worth
Burping so much
And it's like, I haven't been here in a long time ago, so it's like, I'm mad at me, I didn't say shit, why are you mad at me for people saying stuff?
It's like, am I supposed to be mad at people saying something, be the channel about me, which they do all day, and how I'm just like this trash human being?
I know, it was gross, it was gross all night, that was ridiculous.
She's scared with Mason. I think I will take away her lunch. I know I know what you guys it was like
Oh, she might go robo, but ever
Hit scum and other people Dean Dean she I was on your side. I don't know about now and I'm on crystal side. Oh
Please
Christine, I told her it was the car that did it.
I didn't say it was the car.
Christine, I don't know that lady.
I remember being really mean to me one time.
I don't get it, guys. Anyone can tell Crystal's mouth?
I don't know what she was saying.
All I know is that it was a funny-
You're not- oh, Crystal or he's always a mean thing.
Hello.
Hey, Psyche.
How are you doing today?
Good.
Good morning.
How are you?
I was listening to you in the car while I was doing some stuff earlier.
You picked some good clips today when it comes to the mentality of some things that you've
been contending with.
You know, you know how I don't like the term low cow rancher. Just like you don't I
Want to put on a cowgirl hat really bad when it comes to him though. I
Might
Because I don't like guys like that
Especially when they claim to be champions of women of color when in actuality, they're the opposite
With the first time that he came at me. He was saying oh, don't forget you're black and
I thought to myself
What and then I looked at his YouTube page and he tries to add like he's honoring all these black women and everything
No, he wants to use the black women as shields and then control the black women and then weaponize them against his enemies
But if you're not
a stereotypical black woman like he wants you to be,
then he takes issue with you.
But if you ever see this Bronzeberg,
I am so thinking about putting on a cowgirl hat,
getting a lasso and wrangling your ass right in
to Alexandra's range of dumb ass copper birds.
Copperbirds, I'm thinking about it
Someone is saying blame and race is so lazy. Yeah, show us your picture
I bet you couldn't last one damn day in my skin. You sick son of a bitch
But I'm not talking to anybody really. How are you doing today? You did IRL today?
I did I haven't in a while and yeah
you know, it's like
I'm really into McDonald's lately, so
I take the chat on a walk, you know, and so yeah, pretty good and I
Don't have the best. I just use my little cell phone and stuff, but yeah kind of interesting
Yeah, I thought it was good, you know, I like when you take a solid element now. What's this? I hear about you getting ready to meet
LD. I hope you do meet him. He's really cool
Yeah, like the last night he actually was a really funny show last night
He showed up and he was like doing kind of like a POV thing where he's like sitting on the bed
and then there's this woman with like long pink hair like unpacking a suitcase and
I don't know, there was like all this, it was pretty funny.
And then he's like, hey, he's like,
well, we're in LA right now.
Do you wanna maybe hang out tomorrow?
And I was like, yeah, and he turns out to be right
in Long Beach, which is just like one city away pretty much.
And I would love to, I would love to meet him
and I love meeting people in IRL.
I had such a fantastic time with meeting you and.
You know, you're the first person basically from this community that I didn't meet in person and it's like
Well, no, you said you met somebody before me you went to like this community like that that person was like basically
He was kind of like a tarot person and another person's chat that person. I mean, I've just found out like
This guy he was the reason like how do you saying that LD still in Philly?
Are you there in Philly? They were lying? I don't know. He said they're in LA, but maybe I was...
Well, maybe they're headed to LA. Now, LD does travel. Where do I meet up with him?
Las Vegas, Fremont Street. I happened to be out there and he lived really close by. That's how that happened.
But LD travels a lot more than you would think. He's been in Vegas, California,
Texas. Now, supposedly he's in Philly, but as you know, a lot of us who travel a lot,
we don't always tell you where we are or when because of things that you contend with, you know?
So, you're saying it's a prank, Gotti?
Well, he could have just said that, or maybe he meant that he was going to meet with Psyche another time, but LD doesn't really, he's only malicious if he's defending somebody that he cares about.
That's the only time.
He'll only be malicious with when it comes to his sibling and maybe whoever sees he's dating
at that time. But he probably does want to meet Psyche because he saw me meet Psyche,
and I've met him, meaning I'll date him. So that's how it goes.
Yeah, and he was with Simi.
He's always with some interesting woman.
I've never seen this one before.
Yeah, she kind of looks like a kind of like Sailor Moon
or something like that.
But he's like, hey, we can either go to like a bar
at this certain location, or we can go to this cemetery.
You know, and hey, yeah, the cemetery.
I'm like, OK, that sounds cool.
Like, you know, nighttime in the cemetery,
that sounds pretty cool.
But yeah, I did.
Yeah, he's he's really cool and also like Tommy James and I like we never have traditionally got along and I
I did have him like blocked at a certain point
But I ran into him at Kate's and then someone had sent me Tommy James is
Link and he was doing a show and I don't know if he's still has it up
I don't let's take a look was it on his panel channel. Yeah
Is that just Tommy James?
Tommy James channel channel that'll bring it up. Okay. He's live right now
Yeah
Actually, I had a good time on the panel. I went up in the sequel.
Oh, look at this. Someone is saying that I'm talking shit about him.
I'm going to screen-cap this. You know what? Divine intervention. Look at that.
Someone known as Good Times Fan For Life is saying that I was talking shit about Tommy on your panel.
and I said his tongue game is weak.
I've never said that.
You've never said that.
You know what?
See, I'm screen-capping it right now,
and I'm so, you know what?
This was divine intervention to catch the trolling
because you're the trollmaster.
And you wrote Trollopedia, look at that.
I just, and why is everybody talking about me?
Why, every time I go look at a Tripp Kigg video,
Crystal Marie was saying that I slept with good times.
I've never met good times.
I remember she was saying something like that.
Like, I was like, what?
I mean, yeah, that's crazy.
Like, wow.
I think the only thing I've ever heard about,
tell me, James, you were saying that.
is calling me a PDF and you a PDF also saying that we're lurking, we're looking at the chat.
So are there people out there with multiple monitors, multiple keyboards or laptops,
looking at this, looking at other panels, they're like, what can we do?
They do go back and forth fast. Like I know they they're always like if I ever talk about somebody like it's like usually
They're right in their chat saying oh he's saying this and then usually exaggerating or saying completely something wrong, right?
And then it's like the person's like what are they saying and then they come here yelling me. I'm like, I didn't say that
You I did I knew that this was happening, but I didn't know it was like this extreme
This is getting more extreme because some people are scared good. They should be scared
Okay, like I remember you just said like you know you
Walking with Tommy James Winston like you know, you're a fast walker and he was kind of like a slow walker
And I'm very yeah
I've said that because he was saying that I walked so fast like I'm paranoid and I'm like
I don't want that fast and now you walk fast. Maybe it's a January 7th thing
Maybe we just walk kind of fast. I think we're fast walk. We have somebody I've never seen in the chat before captain
Hayden, I'm going to put up a banner real quick and like, Steve, what's up with this person?
Hello? Captain Hayden. Let me see. Who is this? Okay, he's giving you a peace sign? Okay, I think
it's fine. Okay. It's Captain Half Fun, man. We talked the other day, man. Like, I typically wear a
costume, remember? Like, I have my baby boy right now, and so like, you know, I'm just going to kick
That's so cute.
It's so cute.
Someone is saying that I look haggard.
I look great.
Let's see what happens.
Hey, Queen Natalie.
Hi.
How are you doing this morning or where you are?
You look beautiful.
Don't listen to what anyone says.
You look beautiful, Miss Natalie.
You're gorgeous.
Both of you are gorgeous.
People are just ridiculous.
I mean.
they really will just say anything and so just crazy and I'm really getting used to like just
being able to like have anything said about me because you know I think the worst has already
been said basically and so and that even like that's what I liked about Tommy James panel last
night you know he just really does have like a philosophy of like
You know freedom of speech anybody can come up and say anything they want
I mean even he had SIG on and but SIG unfortunately started saying the n-word and so
He kept putting him backstage. I was like, you're not gonna get him to stop. I was like, I had SIG on my show for over a hundred hours
Probably it's it, you know, sitting either sitting on the panel or and it's just like he is just impossible to bring
He actually said the n-word on on Tommy's panel before and then reported Tommy's channel and got Tommy's channel and trouble and so
oh my god that's that's an a-hole
you know anything about rocks
or bones is that a rock
is that from the ocean?
what is that?
it's around it on the beach
oh
It's all the witches stone or something
I remember and these these rocks used to come up on the shore of the beach near me
Call rat beach and they have these holes in them put it put in them by like the sea creatures
And then they become witches rocks or something. That's beautiful. It's like a piece of coral maybe or what is that?
I don't know, but my kids found it on the beach. I don't know what my kids found on the beach.
I don't know if it's rock or bender or awful or what it does. It's like a bone. Yeah, I was about to say if it's porous
I mean, there's just more chances unless the giant
Yeah, is it light or is it heavy? Is it a little heavy? It sounds hollow
It's a piece of coral. Do you guys know about um, oh, I like that picture
Have you guys heard of amber grease
AMber amber grease, you know what that is have you heard of that it washes up on the beach
Amber grease is actually like an ingredient and a lot of uh perfumes and things like that. It is actually a whales
Vomit basically and it hardens and it pulls up on the beat and it's like and they put it in
It's very very valuable to if you find a piece of it
I'll tell you a little bit about it because it's just so interesting amber grease is a see amber grease is
Okay, I'll show you what it looks like too.
It is a solid waxy flammable substance
of a dull gray or blackish color produced
in the digestive system of sperm whales.
Freshly produced ambergris has a marine fecal odor.
It acquires a sweet earthy scent
as it ages commonly like into the fragrance of alcohol
without the vaporous chemical astringency.
it is highly valued by perfume makers as a fixative that allows the scent to last much longer.
And then it's, how much is it worth? It is worth a lot. It is worth, let me see,
Emery Grease Christ. It's like, because if you find a piece of this on the beach wash up,
you know, and it's whale vomit basically, it's or whale poop, it says. Why is it valuable? Yeah,
It says, in 2016, three fishermen from the Middle Eastern country of Oman struck floating
gold in the form of ambergris, traditionally thought to be whale vomit.
It's more like the gallstone poop, it says, but although it's pretty repellent, it is
actually worth big bucks.
The chunk that these guys stumbled upon weighed 176 pounds and was allegedly worth nearly
$3 million.
Wow.
Whale vomit, right?
That is just great. It smells sweet and it's used in perfumes and stuff. Isn't that strange that, you know, they all...
There's something...
That's in Red Bull, that's supposed to be from Wales also
Yeah
Oh my god. Well, there's also I heard Torian, which is where this is bull urine. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Torine Torine Least isn't I'm lucky. I can't stand the taste of anything. I don't like Thailand. So, you know
I can't stand them, I don't know why.
I can't stand them.
You guys know what castorum is?
Have you heard of castorum?
Castorum is also in perfumes and things like that.
It's also artificial raspberry flavor.
It comes from the glands of a beaver's anus
and it's very, very valuable.
Okay, now let's call it.
I used to put this stuff on my face like it was really, really super expensive and it had like
lactic acid and stuff in it, but it also had, I forget what, but it had placenta in it.
Oh my god.
It was just placenta and this stuff was super expensive and you could only get it at like these
like boutique places of Beverly Hills and you know my friend came was like born from old money
and like you know so
Trust Fun Kid, one of those guys, you know, a little Trust Fun Kid.
So he just used to like spend like tons of money and on BS and that was one of the things
that I always have to wonder.
I was like, was that actually really good for my face or was I just putting nonsense
on it?
Like, you know.
Have you heard of the Korean?
What?
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
I use cocoa butter and cream on my skin.
Cocoa butter is so good for your skin.
It's one of the best steps.
Oh yeah, most definitely.
And you've got several kinds of fats.
That's for my hair, it's all good oil.
I
She still like didn't have like any wrinkles like not a single wrinkle you could tell she's older
But she didn't have like wrinkly skin at 70 years old and asked her like what do you do to keep that?
And she's like I just always keep my skin moist like I always put coconut oil or like if I don't have that like even lard
I just always keep my skin moist at all times because
Well, she said, she told me to remember it like this, if you take a piece of paper and you and you
creak it up into a ball and then try to straighten it out, well then it's got wrinkles.
But if you take a piece of paper that's wet, it's the exact same thing, no wrinkles.
There's a nice, interesting powder, it's called Windsor of Woods and it's really nice, you can
Many of the valley where you can get
Rows and there's smell beautiful. It's like a talcum powder and you get a little do you remember those old-fashioned force
Old-fashioned play
I don't know what the colon is.
There's something called EGF, which I've heard about.
Ellen DeGeneres was mentioning it.
It says that it is derived from the proprietor cells
of the human fibroblast taken from Korean newborn baby
foreskin.
That is in the Korean beauty cream.
Ellen DeGeneres uses that.
Yeah, have you heard of that?
That is really bad. Yeah, I wouldn't doubt it is six hundred fifty dollars. Kate Blanchett uses it her favorite six hundred fifty
dollar uses facial uses Korean newborn baby four skins. Oh, I think I was going to go to Lamplacenta or Lamplacenta
It's what I was putting on my face
Lamplacenta. Wow. I mean all kinds of them
I mean like even musk musk, which is like, you know that comes from like, you know, what like a mousse is
You know glands some kind of look that and they put that in perfume all these things are like
What kind of going through?
What kind of what it goes with a go see what kind of
What's I yeah, how's everybody doing? Sorry to join
How you doing Alex
Prefer Alexandra either way, okay
Have you met ghost before ghost is like, you know, it's ghost tober this month and we're having a little party tomorrow
We don't see what's it a 24-hour sure. I don't know
Somebody just put a short out where I was like you're not invited
Everyone's implied it Alex TV are you called Lexi every call you Lexi?
Or Alexandra some people say Alexandra some say Alexandra you can call me anytime by the way
It's okay ghost is like you know ghost one time like you know DJ Electra and I were
We'd be I had no ghost as well. And you know, we
She thought you recognized
Somebody else's voice, you know, this guy Tony
Hey, you know what I will admit it is very similar though. I because I've listened to it
And I was like that kind of does
It does it's not him because he showed us can't you got on camera before but like yeah, when I got really
He doesn't have the right laugh or the right sarcasm or the right debate skills. I mean
Yeah, you can hear his voice actually on the, when he's on the, on the scrap metal stream
on twip kick where he's like, psych, he's going to get the army of scrappers at his
house.
You know, I can't believe you would have said that on tape.
You know, it would be a good panel, me versus Tony.
He used to come on the show.
That would be awesome.
Happy computer.
And that would be great, but uh, you know, I mean I would be willing to but I don't
I want a 1v1 against you
He's always watching I trust me he is always watching he's obsessed with me. I've never it's kind of
Disturbing like how obsessed you have a lot of people obsessed with you right now
Seriously, like well, well, he's pretty darn good
I mean the other day he gave me a reading for free like I mean
I don't normally believe in this stuff
But I told my wife afterwards even she had to have a laugh at it because he was so spot-on. I mean, we're no
normally not like, you know like
But I was like, I told my wife, I was like, oh my God, last night, guess what this guy
said to me?
I told her everything he said psyched, and she goes, what?
It's a certain nothing.
Well, thank you.
Yeah, also there's an IRL streamer named Scribbles.
I don't know if you ever heard of Scribbles,
but I just stopped by his show the other night.
He's a really good looking,
I mean, I think he's a good looking guy,
but give me, he has-
I know your type now.
I know your type.
I figured it out, I didn't like him, okay.
Yeah, but he's like, hey, he's like,
hey, do you feel like coming up
and doing a reading for me?
Cause, you know, and like,
he's never had a reading from me or anything.
And so he ended up like starting a new stream so I could come up on stream yard and then I did a reading for him
And then he's like tells us what his wife. He's like, oh you got to get one too
And so I did a reading for both of them and that was just really smart
Good good a lot of people is it is it is the clip anywhere or yeah, I do have the clip
Maybe if you post the link to the clip
It's on the um my community ball
Oh, okay. Yeah, I definitely want to repost that on the channel because I think you should read everybody in the communities that you know you're kind of like linked to that would be so good for you.
Yes.
Uh, is that a painting behind you or is that like a blanket? What is that?
It's a this is a green screen and I can project any image
That looks cool, so I did generate this image. It's kind of a merry Magdalene a little bit of an image
But uh, I didn't have one question before I have to go there. I want to ask captain a question if you don't mind
Oops
There you go guys talk captain is that your picture? Is that your picture? Do you Google it?
Or is that you?
No, you can look at my channel. That's really me. I really do dress okay
With weights and all that not silly nonsense
What are you trying to do in that picture? It's like a like a I know it's not Ninja Tower because you're blue, but what were we trying to do?
Well, thank you very much.
I mean, I kind of like the way Dr. Fate looks.
And so like my gloves are yellow as well.
And that studio picture's incomplete.
I've actually gained some size.
And the studio I completed, I've
bricked up all the walls and stuff.
And so it looks like almost like a brick alley now.
You know what you're talking about.
Can I use that as my profile pic?
I'm going to call him Captain Dumb Dumb.
Kept it captain. You remind me of banana man
Banana man
I used to get a magic banana and use to eat the banana
In the camera do not flex in the camera, sir
You're making fucking go crazy right now. Don't do that so flat today too. There's no glycogen in my muscles
I need to eat but I've been taking care of this a little one all day because
Wife has gone off. She sees seven or second ultrasound and some stuff done
Congratulations
back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back to back
she's Chinese man and she don't give up so. Oh wow I told you like my sister-in-law is also
she's a Chinese national um you know that came came over here for school lag so I got little
have Chinese nephews in there they're great you know but uh yeah and IVF that's that's no joke
That's a it's a big deal. It's very it's very expensive too and the congratulations on uh,
on those that's amazing
Because we're her it's part of her work
Like that's why like she wanted to do it because like she worked and she wasn't cause for like as long as a doctor for all of her finance stuff
Which I don't really understand why I was like see her like
you don't have to work. You live with me. We're perfectly fine. We live in the hills. We're fine.
I'm in that Hollywood. She just didn't want to live off of me. Also, I agree. I want to buy her
mother a house. I'll pay her half of it, but I want to buy her mom a house here in America
because her mom is great with our son and I just really love her and think that she needs to be here.
Oh, you know I'm trying to actually have all you have to take care of that motherly because in your family
Well, that's that's question for you before I have to go to work real quick. Um, I see that you got a cough on your neck
Are you religious?
Yes
Christian
Okay, I'm actually doing a page by page reading of the bible on my
Alexander Mayer's channel right now. I do it. I try to do a reading almost every day
But I don't always get around to it every day
And you also do the hero card readings as well
No, no, but I'm I feel like there's a lot of astrology and tarot and
People with foresight things like that within the Bible and I think that there's a way for it to mesh together
That's my opinion
I agree. I'm really into like science and like space and stuff like I like my in my free time
That's what I usually like look up. Yeah, and I'm also religious to um
Christian
So I try to like tie it in but it's kind of like, you know, it's kind of like
Usually like if you debate somebody they try to make you like you hey pick a slide
Like, all right, I'll put this on.
I have a spirituality and religion is very personal.
Some people do need to belong to a church.
I actually do belong to a church.
I'm going to keep that to myself,
but I grew up in a pretty spiritually open household,
even though my mom adhered to One Direction
and I feel that my dad was a lot more open.
I've just had a lot of influences over the years when it comes to spirituality of a lot of different ways of thought and
my personal main
Is that you should treat others the way that you want to be treated. I think that's the golden rule, correct?
I think that's the golden rule. No matter what you what you are
I think Alex, you know growing up like that. I'm sorry Mason. Are you saying something my bad brother?
It's like, yeah, I was just saying, hey, let's flip to Alexandria.
Yeah, this is Mason. Yeah.
Yeah, it's hard to grow out.
Would you agree with me? Like when you grow up like that, like from early age,
even if you're not religious, but you know, your parents are,
that's why people say like a higher power.
Like, um, so like people tend to grow up.
They like, I don't think that's necessarily wrong to grow up like that.
Like, even if it's forced on, you know, this a little bit, I mean,
How are you looking for a scrap metal?
Yeah, I'm looking for a scrap metal.
Who just said scrap metal?
I guess I'm not really.
A very unusual environment, extremely unusual.
I do.
And.
I don't expect anyone to think along the lines that I do.
I've come across very few people that do actually,
but I just kind of think that you do need to have faith
in something outside of yourself
because it's gonna take a lot of responsibility
off your shoulders.
It's going to broaden your perspective.
And I feel better about yourself
Well the first the first time
Somebody scared me with it when I was young and
Apologize to Mason you're invited by the way
They pointed out the scariest part in the Bible and you said I'm invited man
Yes, sir. I didn't know because I didn't really I'm really interested in the Bible. Oh
Gosh guys, unfortunately, I just had a guy knock on the door. He was told there's a lawnmower here for sale
That's yesterday there was another lawnmower person here, too
And there's been at least probably over 20 people the last week as it may probably over 20 people's time wasted
But over 10 pizzas, you know, I mean just like what a waste of their time really
I mean it's like more than my time. It's like he's like me or yes. Yes, sir
At least they're not saying I'm thinking it looks like I think Alexander looks like she could be like a psychotherapist or a therapist or
He died
Come back up because I'm getting a lot of feedback and I think it's okay. Okay. Okay. Okay
I remember a time when I was six years old, when I felt the Holy Spirit correct me and
I wasn't taught with Christianity, I was born very pagan and I felt the Holy Spirit correct
me when I was little.
I'll tell you what I was doing, I was being very naughty when I was six.
My cousin was younger than me, she was four.
me and my friend was tormenting her. She wanted to use the restroom and we both went
it was not my idea I was the ringleader. I went into the bathroom.
And I said, let's play a prank on her, let's not let her go to the toilet.
I was in the bathroom with my friend and there was stopping my cousin from using the restroom.
And suddenly something overtook me, made me feel guilty and made me feel really sad.
So I opened the door, I cuddled my cousin.
And the other girl that was copying off me, she directed at the same time, but it's like God corrected us both at the same time.
So you've come back with God's voice? Correct?
Yeah, it was like a feeling. It was like, it was like a feeling that you shouldn't be doing that.
It was gentle, it was gentle, it was kind, and it just made me feel sad for hearing a cry in the bathroom.
Because I believe God is love, you know, and so, yeah, that, it would be like, yeah, exactly how you said, like a loving, gentle correction that gives you empathy almost, and that's beautiful that you.
You heard that voice, you know, and I know you're not going to Natalie. No, no, it doesn't matter.
I remember Natalie was talking about, you know, her experience with some maybe fallen angel
I
Said you look like a sophisticated woman Alexandria, thank you. I try to be I'm actually not but I try I I'm glad that
Look fake it till you make it, right?
Thank you, thank you very much
You're very I mean it like is it a compliment Alexander it is. Thank you. Thank you
Well Alexander, I think you're beautiful
Don't do it. Oh he's doing it a thirst trap
You know even though
When I was a teenager I used to be interested into witchcraft
God still send a Christian to save me on a phone
Are you closing your eyes psyche? Yes, I'm just listening I'm smiling and listen
It's like you're even looking in the camera
Little bit like I have a bright light in my kind of but over here. So I see your eyes. We know you're lying. Those aren't dark shades
We know what you we know what you're looking
I'm closing my eyes a little bit
In your life, yes, I do I've had a buzz cut you should both cut it
Yeah, maybe I shaved my head before but yeah, there are Christian witches. I mean there are
Which is to have a relationship with God, you know, they I mean
I don't know. You shouldn't
be there. You can't be a
that's like you can't do that.
I'm not a witch anymore. I'm
not like you. Are you a
I do now
That's why I said higher power you can't believe in the Christian God and be a fucking pagan and do all this like it
You're born into a household to where wishcraft was always practiced
Let's say that you're even born with a certain ability
But you do have a relationship with God and you believe in things in the Bible some people
She has an awakening
Uh, she felt the power of Jesus. She felt the power of Christ. Uh, like you can't, like, yeah, if you grow up, like, oh, the witchcraft stuff, but once you feel that power, I mean, there's like, all heads, all bones, all tongues.
Well, I mean, if you're asking about that kind of stuff, I mean, my mother was originally a Jew and I was raised Christian Christian, but I mean, I mean, I was born on a very particular day for the
Anyway, uh, yeah, uh, it was very strange growing up in that, uh, you know, I still like I went
I had to get my own baptism and she she didn't support that. Um, but you know, like, yeah, it was
I mean, I if you have questions when it's like have a witch mother and a christian grant a dad and family like
I can kind of answer that for you
Natalie did you get a situation you can't really I mean sometimes people do fit certain stereotypes, but everyone's situation is different and I don't think you can really
Justifiably say that there can't be a certain thing because if your mind can give it it most likely exist
Well, you're not Christian if you pull a tear apart. There's actually a scene in the Bible when I
Well, there's a lot of prophecy though in the Bible people who were considered to be seers
Later were redefined as prophets in the Bible and a seer often does utilize
things like tarot or astrology. I mean astrology is
that means you produce the future. There's no profits anymore.
Alexander what would you make of this? I mean I think Ploxomany matters and this
is probably more along lines or no viewing kind of thing but but when I
was a kid I mean like my dad was was an intelligence person for the military
all this stuff but we were close we were in Atlanta
and I said we're not going to go to the olympics we can't go to the olympics and
We knew there was going to be a fucking bomb and when the bomb went off, we were not surprised whatsoever.
It was just kind of like, oh, it's going to rain tomorrow.
Interesting.
You know what? There's a female prophet in the Bible that's never mentioned.
I'll tell you who it was.
Which of Endor?
Hannah.
You know Samuels mother she prophesied the end she prophesied and it's in one Samuel chapter 2
Verse 10. Oh you want to Google it. You really want to go and let's do it
Oh, here's another thing. It was kind of odd as my father and I both knew Richard Joel didn't do it
He had nothing to do with it whatsoever
And every time they were saying Richard Joel may have it on the it was making us very angry because like I was like
It's like that man as a hero. He had nothing to do with the bombing
And he shall rain pundas
He shall rain pundas or something
What is what do you believe in man like what is your belief like are you a christian or what is your like religions?
I believe that religion is like a boat
and that you can, there's many kinds of boats, right?
And you just use it across, you know, an ocean
to get to the other side.
Once you get to the other side,
you really don't need the boat anymore, right?
It's like, and I believe there's many ways.
You know just as many people as there are there's that many divine everyone different different way
I do believe in like a higher power. I believe in the all I believe I believe everything has gone
I believe God is love
You know Jesus is God. I don't understand the old trinity be the trinity be
What don't you understand about it that um confuses you because I'll talk about that well
How can Jesus be called and be left by God on the cross when he couldn't look upon his thing
I don't understand that bit well the initial goal was for um there to be a clean slate for humanity
and for there to be a way for everyone to start over again.
And that's what Jesus's role initially was,
was to experience what it is to be in the flesh
and then to basically take on everyone's sins
past, present, and future.
That way everyone going forward would be able to,
not only have free will, but just,
And I have to carry the weight of so much that it happened prior to Jesus's arrival because there was a lot go
I mean, I don't know how much you've read at the Old Testament. I mean, it used down like you know everything
about
Before
You can see it's playing in this world because the Bible says that you're not supposed to follow your own heart
and your heart's desire because your heart is truly wicked.
Who would know it?
And if you do go on YouTube, follow your heart.
Look how many cartoons we've watched all our lives,
which has been in grooming us to say that we should follow our own hearts.
Can you define grooming real quick, if you don't mind, go ahead.
Like programming, programming nothing, we've been programed all our lives by, do you know?
Just real quick before I forget this, I have an issue on Alexandra,
you're great at putting into just a few words, but would take many.
I hope it works like you, I love you, I just think you find that.
Thank you.
Sorry, I mean to interrupt you Natalie, sorry.
Oh, I'm just listening to Natalie.
When I used to go to school in assembly, they used to, I didn't mind seeing him, but when I went to this church of England school, when they made us sit crossing our legs to pray, I wasn't comfortable with that.
And I watched have you ever watched spike it and TV where you're actually doing the madras sign
When you when you're crossing your legs and you pray pray it's actually a it's actually a mudra sign
And
People aren't gonna like this but the
The Roman Catholic Church and the Orthodox Church have been mixing paganism with
Christianity
Just so they could make money. So they've been profiting on people's
beliefs
Well, when it comes to religion, religion was initially one of the first quote-unquote
businesses.
The oldest businesses are religion, if you want to call it that, because it has become
that today.
Being an attorney and being a prostitute, those are the three oldest professions.
Being a hunter. I mean like if you were really good at hunting, okay
To kill things for them, right, right
Yes, Mason
Do you actually have your own channel like psyche has this channel and stuff like that? Yes. Yes. It's my name
Alexandra mayors
What exactly do you talk about on there, though, just about different things or different topics?
My own Tondra Mayer's channel has always really been about my life and my personal interest and my art, really.
IP to wiki info initially was just kind of me trolling certain communities and then it kind of became
something else
So that's Andrew. Is that how you became friends like with site because y'all well talk about the troll stuff. Um,
I initially came across psyche through beat us channel
That's how I initially got to know psyche and then one night psyche myself and Goddy
all had a really good conversation and it just really was a very clarifying conversation
to me.
And then ever since then.
It's like, is that right then?
Of course.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
We just clicked right away.
We have the same birthday basically.
So it's like, yeah.
That's a big part of it.
Hey, thank you, Arbiter, for the $20.
Ghost always wins.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
That's awesome.
I really appreciate you.
Thank you.
We're not Georgia there saying she's the next old star.
Well, I don't know why people think that that bothers me.
If anything, that is my living proof that once upon a time,
I was a really hot young thing, you know?
So, hold up, hold up, hold up, hold up.
I used to be a photographer for Penthouse, Hustler.
I mean, I worked with him over at World Modeling.
10 house and hustler when not the Cosby's came out that's when I have my first oh oh oh my god okay not the Cosby's isn't okay I play the mom but my space name was Monica I was on that yeah okay so is that is that not trying to remember his I mean it's the guy for the Brady bunch right is that Jeff Mullen is who directs it will right.
Will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will, will
Alexander doesn't make sense because you said you used to look like you were good before but you still looked that way though
So I'm not
Mason if I could give you a giant hug right now. I would I really would
Thank you. Thank you. Yeah, but yeah, but Alex Andrew. Why would you like doubt yourself and say you look better before when he's still
No matter what you do no matter how much money you spend you can never get one thing back
And that's time which equates to youth
Thank you. I donated five dollars if you can get alex out of here for five minutes
Okay
Can I use it some other time I could redeem it some other times like
Thank you. Thank you psyche. No problem. Oh, there's a reason why because of the evil one who just cannot get a reader
Can I get a reader? Huh?
I don't want to literally I don't want to read I got the rebel on is that the rebel on
So you're sticking up for Alexandria, right?
Yeah, what you're my Mason mind your business papa relax
Don't talk to him like that Sam
Whoa
About me you don't think I hear I'm just well you lie on me Alex Alex you lied on me
You call me all this and all that you'd be lying on me. I'll be shut your mouth
Acting like we had all these conversations
I didn't say that I privately twice boy. All right. All right. Shut up. Alex
Like you don't need people throwing jackets on you when you throw jackets on everybody
You're affiliated with so many people that have been unjustly throwing jackets on me that it is crazy
But I have nothing else to say to you Sam man. Excuse me. I can hear my
Excuse me while you're yelling excuse me Alex
You put Trisha up, you exposed Trisha, you exposed Big T, now you cool with them, Jess
J.
You can't hate me.
So back mom's club, feel you.
I don't fear you Alex. I don't fear you Alex. I don't fear you Alex. I don't fear you Alex. I don't fear you Alex. I don't fear you Alex. I don't fear you Alex. I don't fear you Alex. I don't fear you Alex. I don't fear you Alex. I don't fear you Alex. I don't fear you Alex. I don't fear you Alex. I don't fear you Alex. I don't fear you Alex. I don't fear you Alex. I don't fear you Alex. I don't fear you Alex. I don't fear you Alex. I don't fear you Alex. I don't fear you Alex. I don't fear you Alex. I don't fear you Alex. I don't fear you Alex. I don't fear you Alex. I don't fear you Alex. I don't fear you Alex. I don't fear you Alex. I don't fear you Alex. I don't fear you Alex. I don't fear you Alex. I don't fear you Alex
Damn read the room. Bye. Bye. We're cooking over here. Dang
Can we cut I'm just saying Alex you called me PDF
almost all types of shit Alex
What you doing the beat up is a sight what you didn't beat I have to do with
Look at what to me. Do you are you trying to I'm just asking we can have a conversation Alex, you know
Alice, you know, I can have a conversation, you know that you know more than anybody. I can have a conversation. Yes, I can
Okay, let's have it the conversation
About what seven years ago when you had your Yu-Gi-Oh cards, what?
My god
Mesa they change your shirt. So Alex, I'm just saying I've been told you why you lie on people you you go
You constantly
Alex is crazy
Alex is crazy you play everybody clips and when people play your cup you get mad. That's your fun
Do you know that deal? Why is that? Why are you mad at me? Alex? I'm having fun
You're so fake. It's ridiculous. I think that you're actually fake her then beta
day
What you want me mad at me to pick a site, you know that
Was trying to put a hit out on me and it came out
What's the hit Alex come on Alex, what's the hit clumsy will tell you all about it you believe comes in I sure do
Why
Because I was not always okay with clumsy. Did it didn't make a wiki a clumsy expose in his minor family members
Alex
I hit girls, what girl I hit?
You're hitting me right now,
but you're not doing it successfully.
Alex, I'm hitting you how?
You absolutely are, you're attacking me for no reason.
What?
Yeah.
And why?
I don't know how to believe myself.
Adam, you laughing, see?
You laughing, see?
I'm going to believe myself now so you can talk.
I'm trying to believe myself.
Macy, shut the fuck up.
I'm your brother.
Because you are not my equivalent until you can't believe.
Shut up.
Why are you telling me that?
I'm going to believe myself.
I'm eating a hot dog. I don't want Alex. Do you have a conversation? I'm gonna do
I think he fancies you cut he's got the horse for you
Didn't you beat your dog ain't this the female that be her dog?
You sure okay
You talk about your friend who called me a pdf since 2022 who killed a dog neglected
Who did who did?
Amber didn't kill Amber they killed dog Alex. Stop lying on my 225 you hurt stop lying on
my 225 you hurt lie on my 225
Amber is sober Alex. Amber is sober Alex is sober Alex. I mean amber is sober Alex
dog. Where is the dog? Yeah.
What's up?
Clean up your dog, man. Clean up your channel before you lose it.
Yes, out to the thrice.
Nice.
London.
I mean, go to London.
Am I Google?
No.
Yes.
Well, look, and you're smiling.
Look, look, Alex, you think you're tough.
Look, look.
I can't smile.
I always smile.
You think you're tough.
I ain't scared of you.
I got the red balloon.
I got the red balloon, Alex.
I'm not a bad mom.
So I don't have to fear you.
So I don't fear you.
Pennywise the clown?
People are a-
The only one who fears me is the bad mom. It's the bad mom. Big T, Big T, Trisha, Trisha,
Jess, Jess.
We're the leader of strong black women.
Wow.
Not until recently did you even define yourself as black?
I love my black woman. I love cockroaches.
I see that you define yourself as black now.
is to try to counter the people who have called you out about it but you weren't black before
you were saying that you were latino and what else something after a latino you were saying
something but now suddenly you're black that's i'm black i'm white michael jackson i'm black
Should have faced Alex if I'm the punter of the year.
Hey, this is my first time I can actually have a conversation with you.
With all that slander.
All that slander you throw at me.
And I tell you, Alex, I told you this, you can't control me.
Alex, I told you you can't control me.
I had no problems with you.
Yes, you do.
You want to control me baby in the wind you're nothing
Like you want to get hooked and I never hooked you like what the fuck you want to control me
You I know that you've done and what scares you is that there is going to be a solid outline of
Everything that you've done. Oh it's complete with clips
Yeah, what I what I what I have done you put lies on me allegation jackets
I don't lie on you Alex your people do nothing but put Jack your people by the way your people
me Alex
Including Alex judge me Alex. Why you don't judge me? Oh
Sam and I'm done talking to you for the day
Well, what are you done talking? I'm going to go ahead and meet my man. Oh
Hey, he's gone
Okay. Alexandria. You got your point across. Yes, Mason. You know, so, so, so we're still cool, right?
Alexander, like, you have no problem with me. Oh, I have no problem with you, Mason. I don't feel the pressure at all.
He, he punches the punks off you, honey. But I don't get it though, Alexander. Why was he telling me that?
But I intimidate him a lot, and he knows that he's pushed a certain...
Gate open when it comes to me, and I just haven't dealt with him yet. I'm waiting
Mason the person who just left the channel Sam man is someone that you should never pay any mind to
complete jerk
But he's being rude to me Alex Andrea for nothing. He doesn't present himself. Well, I'll tell you that
I don't know. I don't know what's going on here, but I cannot tell you automatic. I'm taking your side Alex
Thank you
I do wait I I plan
But I told you that earlier, right? I told you that I was on your side earlier too though, right? Yes, you did Mason
Am I in Hollywood right now? No, I'm not in Hollywood.
Oh, okay. I mean, I'm in Hollywood or like, I don't know. I mean, LA counties or whatever.
You don't even tell me where you are.
I was just kind of wondering if you were like close by because it's just so funny that you know some of the same people I do work for the same people.
I bet you work in the same studios.
We probably walk the same.
Probably.
Well, let's just see here, like, I mean, you know, Ben or, well, over at LA Direct, I was actually, you know.
Well, look, I never was an LA Direct girl. You know what happened about how many years ago.
Oh, yeah, I know you got arrested finally, finally.
There's a woman in this community who was instrumental in that situation.
or Bobby. She used to be known as Bobby and it's actually her brother who is connecting
with Psyche.
Jen and there were some others other girls
Were involved in that I covered that when I was running porn today. I mean, that's why I know
He hated me a lot specifically because I said stuff like like like I mean I
Because the whole I mean when I first started like because I started out really really young I
was 15 in college, okay? And when I was taking my, and I got my avid editing certification
and all that kind of crap for mass media production. And so, I mean, when I came out to Hollywood,
I was 19, and I automatically had the certifications to get work. And my buddy got me working,
being a camera guy, and you know, you just, as long as you know what it was like back and like
But I mean, what it was like to be, you know, as long as you, you were nice, you could get work.
I got, oh, you know, James Dean, the young, when I met him, he was a barista. Okay.
Really?
And he was driving a Saturn, a burgundy Saturn station wagon that you had to have the heat on
to drive it or else it would overheat.
Oh, that's funny.
But because I met him at his very first shoot with the VFX, his agent Scooby didn't get
him work.
I'm the guy who got him work.
I wrote every company I worked for because I loved him because he was my age, so hanging
on set all day long, I wanted someone my age there.
All the young girls because he looked so just like boy next door, but but you were friends with that's funny
I have a picture of him because I we were on shoot and like and like I'm the guy who's holding him up over like the
Girls dressing room set where like so you can look down
And we were laughing because you know the camera sees one thing and then the BTS camera sees all you know me holding him up
because he's not really standing there like like looking over this that long.
That's funny. He really started to get a lot of traction when that Farrah Abraham thing happened.
Remember that? Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, definitely.
Yeah, it's so funny that we know a lot of the same people man. I know I'm still just Stephanie and I used to do karaoke every every
Like it's like Tuesday night over at Sardos and Bird Bank. I used to go to Sardos. I've never crossed paths. I bet we did. I bet we did.
I bet so. Do you know do you know James Barley?
Oh, yeah, we were going to move to that's how that's how I learned about sardos. I used to be one of his girls and then I
Was not but for a while. I got you would always see me and misty together
Misty stone and we were both in that um, cost thing together. Yeah
Okay, so like one time I actually yelled at James like straight out just like yelling and screaming in him because I had a fever and it was five in the morning.
And we're trying to get this shit shot for your will of all people. And I just, I just yell at him and you know we remember Will's little assistant with a dark hair.
Any bullshit right now? I want to go home. It's five in the morning. Stop it because he was like screwing around acting all gay with Seth Gamble
And I don't know what they were doing, but like whatever. I was just like over it
I'm like you're making like each shot like like can we just shoot please?
And because we'd already been there for, you know, way, way too long and like we'll ask like, please don't.
Well, the thing about being in a will writer movie is that once you do that, or at that time, at least that was what put you on the map.
So, you know, that's why people put up with it.
And then like, I mean, if you remember his little assistant
with like the long black hair, like like that his channel,
like I will, at one point, like when we were cut,
like for a break, they both walk up to me to go,
thank you so much for yelling at James,
because we couldn't say that, but you know, you could.
And he's not going to sue you.
Well,
I mean, I love James. So get me wrong. I mean, he was my acting coach for a movie once.
So I think I knew we worked on how I met your mother. I don't know if you knew he was on
there or not. He did an episode of that. I did not know that. No, he played. I forget
the character's name. The not the main character, the one who's kind of like a little bit bigger
with like blonde curly hair, the Jewish guy. I don't know what he says, but the other and
he actually got more work than anybody. But he played his like, like this ghost that spoke
So it was pretty fun, but yeah, man, it's so weird that we know a lot of the same people
and worked on the same thing.
Well, it's a small world.
It's a really small world, you know, I like reminiscing and thinking about certain things
because everyone who brings up, not everyone, but a lot of people, the majority who bring
up that time of my life, they're always so negative, but I have good times when along
questionable times at that time of my life.
But Will and Scott,
I hadn't thought about Scott in a long time.
Yeah, Scott David, yeah.
I was actually more so friends with Scott than Will.
I went out with Will a couple of times.
You know, I worked with him,
but I always gravitated more towards Scott.
Because Scott was more-
Come on, Will had to have hit on, I know he liked black girls.
Oh yeah, well, like I said, I went out with Will a couple.
Will liked me a lot, too much.
But I'm not, but we actually butt heads at one point
because of some things.
But no, I always gravitated more.
Like me and Scott were buddies.
I actually got one of my first.
Wardrobe production credits because of Scott because I did so much of the wardrobe on not the Cosby's
That they were like well, we're not just gonna pay you we're gonna put you a production credit
So I was like cool cool and that opened the door for me when it came to other stuff that I did
So I'm kind of partial the sky opposed to will I just say I mean we'll invite me to the
Halloween parties and like you know, I said I was born on Sawan. So, you know, it's kind of that thing
it's it's the only kind of like birthday party that I have in this town because
You know, Halloween's got to be the worst birthday for anybody in LA. I mean this male, you know, unless you're like a rich superstar
so
Because everybody knows more than you.
Well, Alexandria.
Yes.
You ever want me to ever come to your channel ever, though?
Like even one time?
Any time you want.
It's a public channel.
You're welcome to come to the channel.
Anyone can come to the channel as long as they, you know.
It's like you come to your channel, Alexandria.
It's fine. Please do come to my channel.
I'm asking if Psyche comes to your channel. Does Psyche?
Yeah, that's where we did the three-part series.
Yes. I did a great series with Alexandria.
We talked about some interesting topics in there.
I love those shows.
Those are up there on IRL News Time.
I did post her channels in the chat, everybody.
You sure like you she's part of the psyche verse, right? The psyche universe or what is that called?
My gosh, I have the I have the website almost ready to go
I mean, it's almost just like how I want it and I'm really excited
I've got her channels up there and I want to also help other people in the community that you know
It's a it's a I think a great alternative to IP
but with like, you know less chaos and you know a lot a lot of a
More supportive friendly or a vibe and mission, you know, it's not gonna be but the IP to nonsense
You know that is going on
So I hope that it the I hope that it turns out to be a great great alternative
It's psycheverse org by the way, and it's it's up right now. You can
It's just still, you know
It's just my name Alexandra mayors Alexander mayors IP to wiki.info and
And IRL news
Yes, everyone please sub up and say hi, she has great one interesting and in-depth shows. Yeah
These are everyone subscribed to all her channels. Oh
You are yeah, Alexander mayors live. I see you. Um, you've got quite a few subscribers there, ma'am
Yes, sir, I
Take my time with my channels. My channels are kind of like wouldn't go live a garden
I just kind of grow them slowly
Hopefully when my mother-in-law comes back, I'll be able to start broadcasting from my studio
Which I just in the private chat if you look I posted a picture of my studio
You'll see stuff in there from like all the way back to like the 60s
That I have on the walls is still in the box and stuff
That's just what I do
But anyway
What is what you go live? When do you go live? Oh, I don't have a schedule just whenever I want
You know whenever I feel like okay time to do a Bible reading
I'll do that if I have something on my mind. I feel like complaining about I'll stream about that if I
It's it's random. It's I need to just do consistent streams on my
Alexandra channel a lot more, but I just
Maybe this month, maybe.
It's your boyfriend.
Boyfriend? Uh-oh.
I hear everybody fine.
Psyche, your website looks really good.
I'm like, oh, thank you so much.
Yeah, I'm just trying to get it all perfect.
It's still a little, got a few things to do on it.
But yeah, I think it's going to be really great.
Hopefully it will show when people are alive.
That's what I did like about the IP2 website.
And that's what I really thought IP2 was.
I thought it was a way to promote streamers
within a community, but I didn't know
you know, farming they do and the kind of the negative thing with the, you know, the
IPQ chat always wins and kind of stuff.
I, there's a lot of it is so negative that I'm chaotic that I wanted to have, have a
something for, you know, my friends and people in this community that I really want to support.
And yeah, I hope that hopefully it will be a great, a great thing for everybody.
Really hope so. Yeah, it will be. Thank you
Yeah, and if anyone has a channel they you know, and they would like you know, like it's beyond there
You know just hit me up and let me know about your channel and
if it's right from fit for it, but
But I got definitely got great channels up there right now and looking forward to adding a lot more
I'll just put that a jalapeno and it's loading off.
I have to take a sip of my...
I will be right back.
Yeah, Alexandra.
I see a great Keanu Reeves quote.
It says, life is not about being rich, being popular,
being highly educated, or being perfect.
It's about being real, being humble, and being kind.
Yes, I agree.
Yes.
just came across that. Oh gosh. How's it? Are you doing good this morning, Mason? How's
your morning going, Mason? It's going okay. Wait, it's already afternoon now though,
so it's not morning. Oh yeah, it's afternoon now. I gotta make some more coffee. I'm a little...
What are you? Are those like chips that you're eating with salsa or cheese?
It's got guacamole cheese nacho cheese sauce on some cheese Doritos
Ghost they've pulled your side again, I can't hear this
Oh there goes it says
What did they say Keanu it's a getting pussy
Yeah, okay. I can't see the whole thing Keanu. It's about getting pussy or something like that. Wow, okay
Yeah, go space Killa here. I know who is true. I true identity everyone know that's a our favorite a
Quick quick change costume artist, right? Oh
Yeah, so I key yes, sir
Sike, you always want to go and camera that much now because uh sand man I think if they miss he always tells me hey you got to change your shirt when I have my shirt on and stuff like that.
Sike, will you do a reading for captain.
Because I
He's still one before you see and he was like I said he was absolutely correct. It made my wife laugh
Did I use a whore deck? I'm not captain. Do you mind getting a reading? I'm getting you a read. It's totally cool. It's fine
Thank you very much for asking
Yeah, let's see what I got for captain. I don't know how to be embarrassed
Okay, okay. Well, we have with it with the death card and so there's like some kind of the transformation
And you know, this is an interesting death
It doesn't look like I mean it's like he looks like he's kind of playing the piano right there
But it's it and I think there's these people going up the stairs right there. And so this is like
Really about it says this is the end and the beginning. Okay, and it's like
so you know people get kind of scared of that card sometimes like but it's not you know well
you know i i look at it like this because it's very very apt is we're dealing with death right
now it's so odd um my my grandmother-in-law is dying who i i i very much love i mean i i've
given her like like she she said she told me i'm the only person to ever give her a massage in
her life um which was odd um but like it's like you know i got giant hands and sending
Um, so, so, yeah, I really, really love her and she's dying and we have a son, you know, like my wife and I, and, and like, I don't really want my son to go to China right now.
Um, he's only nine months old and you know, if you knew who my dad was, if they ever found out just like, but I don't know what happens that they would definitely snatch him.
And so like they're just like the whole idea worries me like and it's a conflict with my wife and I do
I say my dad says do not let him go there
Do not let him go and I'm saying I don't want him to go and my mom my wife is saying, you know, you know
I want him to see my grandmother before she dies and like he's not gonna remember it
You'll get it on video, but we might not get him back
Yeah
so I mean because
I would say trust your instincts.
Trust your instincts.
Yes.
Yeah, I'm saying no. I mean, just because I don't, I don't, I'm not a gambler by any means necessary. I do not gamble. So if there's a chance and something like the thing I love the most could be ripped away from me, I ain't taking a damn chance.
Next, we have the page of wands, and this is about new ideas, new energy, and limitless
potential in free spirit, which is, you know, I would say, well, especially after the Death
basically goes feed into that transformation idea of this like this limitless potential something that is going to grow into something
you know infinite and
This the beautiful limitless energy in there, too. Okay, we have a the Sun card. Okay, so
And I know you're holding your son right now,
and oftentimes the son card does have the young child
or the young boy on it.
It's the most positive card in the deck.
And it says, a symbol of vitality, positivity, success.
Life is difficult, but not everything is sickness.
The son is a powerful force that compels
us forward through time. Okay. And just like a sun can, right? We also have a number six
of wands. And this is a victory card. This one is victory at what cost, but I would say
a victory is usually a very positive thing. You just want to always make sure that it's worth
You know winning a fight worth winning. Okay, but there is a victory coming definitely. What else do we got?
The world card the world the world is about the completion of a cycle
And the and the entrance of a new one. It's almost like it is like, you know
Related related almost to the the fool car, which is like the the card zero
This is also like the last card of the major arcana and it's it's a perfect
You can see like it's like the eye here. It's like a
Gateway and it's like a the revolution and like also
We're constantly going through these cycles, but this is the successful completion of a cycle in the end the beginning of a new one
Okay
See what else we got?
We have the emperor. This is the this ultimate authority
And this is this one says ultimate authority rests with him and the emperor card. It's about
Basically all the kings in the deck in it. I would say this is representative of of of you
in that you are able to
I mean, just even when you've talked about all the amazing things you're doing and, you know,
and able to do it into this world, it's like you're a force in this world, definitely.
And you've got definitely the authority and the respect.
Also temperance, which is saying, you know, you're able to alchemize the
Any kind anything negative you can turn it into a positive also about a balance
Okay, and also I would say, you know
One foot in the spirit world one foot in the material world and you know
You're definitely bringing bringing these people through the spirit world into them into this into this material world
We also have
the Ace of Swords, this is the truth.
Either learning the truth about something,
speaking the truth, knowing the truth,
or, and this is the truth, okay?
But also standing up for the truth.
And it is a sword, right?
Because the sword of truth can cut through
any kind of illusion and negativity.
Also, this Empress is popping out.
If we have the Empress and the Emperor together,
I would say
You know, definitely, I would think this is you and your wife, but this Empress is also all the Queens in the deck
Empress's fertility, right? And it's like you're definitely dealing with this is fertility too
Empress card usually I would say is somebody expecting a baby when you get the Empress card, but and yes, you know
I definitely you already said you are okay
We have the Naya pinnacles this is the in the lap of luxury, okay, and so this is just the abundance around you
the beauty around you
Right, you know, I live like in a mini resort, so I think I told you that yeah
I have my own, like a commercial grade gym in my house, a giant pool, all this stupid crap.
Nice.
Yeah, been for years.
Yeah, it is what it is, but you know, family is the most important thing, you know, most important of all.
Well, yeah
Friends friends friends is another thing, you know, I'd give a lot of the money and things I have
Away if I could bring back a few friends and a few family members. I'll take it out
Uh-huh. Well, I just got a couple queens as well the queen. I didn't know and that that is also very very goes along with the Empress
in that she's all four queens and we already got two of them popping out right now like this is
like the passion and also uh the the uh intelligence and communication okay um and so these might be
like the uh the major points that is making about this about this emperors right there
I'm gonna pull a couple more
We have the nine. It's also this is about this is about protecting what you have and you know
I say this is very I think there's a gate, you know, it almost looks like a gate
You know, this is the protection. This is like a this very protective spirit. I would say you have over everything
And we have justice and justice is also this holds that sort of truth and it's like and you will be receiving justice
You know, it could be something in a legal matter, but it also could just be these the karma
You know working out in your favor and things being made totally fair for you. I'm gonna put one more card word of advice for you
Okay, and we have the Five of Pentacles, okay?
And so the Five of Pentacles is about, you know,
sometimes it's about being left out in the cold,
being left out in the cold or something,
but this is like just like, I guess I would say,
you know, make sure that you're not,
not neglecting your own self.
And, you know, I feel like it's like a very,
it's telling you to be very, very welcoming and,
Make sure and I think that the word of advice is to
Not leave anybody out in the cold and make you know, and I don't think you I don't think you are it's an interesting
card to come up with there because
Well, no, I mean, it's always good because it's like, I mean, I don't want to, you know, ever do that.
No.
I live by a few, by a few strict rules, it's like, I live by, do no harm to anyone, nor physically or mentally.
There are living with no indulgences, meaning, I mean, I use to drive exotic cars and like all that kind of stuff. And with the exception to my house, which I, you know, I fought a long time ago, really, I said, like, I'm not allowed to spend more money on something than the average person would.
So, like, even though I could afford to buy an exotic car, that will be a whole move to me now. I just look at, like, well, what else could I do with the, I mean, I could take.
I mean I first for $100,000 like what could I really do with that money besides car?
I mean you can buy a good car that's attendable for 10 grand or less, you know
Well, I think that yeah, I think that's I think it's all looking very it's looking very good and
You know, you got a lot of exciting things coming. I just see you know
I really do see this theme of like this this new life and being being brought through and
You know
Yeah
Also, my third one is but my third one is never look at or touch another man's girl
Ah
Very wise that's a very wise thing, you know, it's Andrea
I hope you like that reading oh
I do it it was spot-on and awesome dude like you got some sort of weird connection brother because like a lot of people have
Like give me readings over the years and wanted to talk to me and stuff
But almost all of us are like I don't know
And you're sticking out amongst like one of my buddies who I've been friends with for
20 years just to just turn 80 like like yesterday, like and and and he has been very, I don't
know if he's got a real connection to God or what but he's been very
like almost like a psychic about my life.
And like, he told me, he's like, him and like,
everybody's gonna go, you're gonna marry this girl.
And I said, no way, no way.
Uh-uh, no.
Cause back in the day, I was a bit of a player
and I didn't look at things the same way.
I bet sure enough, my wife didn't give up.
And yeah, we got married and had kids.
Can you hear me, Alexandria?
Yes, I can, Mason.
I have something I need to tell you, Alexandria.
Go ahead, Mason.
There's somebody there's somebody that's named Ray that's telling me like stuff about you
And I just told him that I didn't want to mess with it because you're doing stuff like it talking and stuff
So
What is this in the chat because I'm not looking at yeah, I'll look at the chat. Let's see
Yeah, talk about the chat. Alexandria. He's like he's trying to tell me to talk to you
But I'm saying that you're busy and stuff Alexandria. So that's why I'm not doing anything
Okay, he's saying that you're beautiful and you're single.
Let me see.
Psych is the best tarot car reader.
Just to sum up my statement.
So spot on, man.
Dang, you just creeped me out.
To the person in the chat, Ray.
Mason's a little bit too young for me, but.
Alexandria.
How old are you, Alexandria?
I'm in my 30s.
I'm almost 47.
almost forty-seven. Shut up you
liar. No, I'm telling you the
truth. I'm twenty-six. Seventy-nine.
I'm kidding, babe. So, you're
too old for me, Alexandra. Yeah,
but if I'm ever in your city and
you want to go for coffee or
lunch, I would love to take you
for coffee or lunch, Mason. But I
could never date you though,
Alexandra.
Nobody can date me Mason
Nobody can't I'm undate of all where I'm not dating. I'm not dating. I'm
single and unavailable
Okay, I
Was just not saying that because that guy in the chat was telling me to talk to you about if you were single and stuff like that
So I don't know
Well, I am single I'm unavailable
And that's about it. But pretty much everyone wants Mason. So everyone wants you, Mason. I've been noticing this. You're like the hot boy right now.
Yeah. I thought that was Psyche though. No, Tantra, I thought that was Psyche though.
No, Psyche's the one that's that way.
Wow
That's Alexandria as a man
I think I think me as a woman and you as a man would be a cute couple, you know
Actually, I have a family member who looks like this AI does a good job
I was gonna say I do have something because I know you're having a new channel and everything
I don't I hope you're not I hope you don't mind this
I just made I had this idea like of you know
I thought about Atlantis a little bit and you know post site in and or you know napkin Neptune and everything
I do have this this image that I generated. I just hope that you
Well, I'm gonna take it. Let me see if I have it. Oh my gosh.
Have you guys seen those 3D ultrasound images of babies?
Yeah.
Oh, the 3D ones? Yes.
They're freaking.
Yeah, it's double-spec. Yeah.
I mean, because like the one that looks like,
well, the one of my son, it still looks like him now.
I was like, I was holding him up like really close to my face
yesterday. I looked over my wife and I was like,
oh my God, it still looks like him.
Have you used the AI to see what your child is going to look like as an adult?
No, I was going to do that the other day.
Do it.
I mean, yes, yes, yes, yes, because I want to do that.
I was talking to my wife just about that because I was like, well, let's see what he's going to look like because I'm just kind of curious.
But also he has like really, really large hands. I mean, I wear a size 14, 15 size shoes and like my hands are about as big.
so you know um and anyway like in the picture of him do it he's he he's got his hands near
his face he's like he's like doing this thing with his hands and in like he still does that now
Yeah, well, he was he was a little you know when they come out it's the same thing as when they were in the womb pretty much
It's just older. Yeah
You know, there's some scientists who question and I know it's evolution, but they question why
We're not more developed as we you know come out the womb because most
Living creatures when they're born they can already walk
and do stuff, but we're
We're the most vulnerable. Yep. Yeah, he's like, yeah, we're the most vulnerable there is when we're born. Yep
And that's why our parents have to see if you can cure of us
Yeah
Yes, yes mason
I'll just say it says that Natalie just went live now and it showed up like in the you know, you know, you too
Yeah, we're gonna check out Natalie soon. I just want to show this uh, this is uh, this is just something maybe to
I don't you're you can just oh here we go. What do you think about this Alexander? Look I love that yeah
That reminds me of the little mermaid in a way like when the little mermaid is hanging out with her dad and stuff
That looks like
Me I love it
I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it. I love it
Have you you know, you know, you know intractable Mason, you know this guy. Yeah, good dude. Yeah, it's like yeah, I talked to him before yeah
Yeah, he's a great dude
Well, it's hanging out here. It's a lovely Friday morning. Hey, it's it's October. You know, it's like we got Halloween coming up
Paul in the fall coming up the leaves are looking beautiful
The weather's nice. Uh, you know, we're just blessed to bless to be alive today and with all you guys
Psychic. Yes. Yes, sir
You didn't know like us now
They just went like on on her channel to actually go like, you know, like on stream
I think or on on on the channel
Huh her channel. Yeah, everyone make sure to check out Queen Natalie. Queen Natty. Is there her channel? It's called Queen Nassie
I'm gonna try to find her like I'm because I'm never I end like she's actually on a thing
Yeah, I'll send everybody over there when I am when I end a little bit, but yeah, definitely. She you know, she's just a
Very very, you know, we you know, she's wonderful interesting person, too
And you know, I want to thank her for being on the show today and you know all of you
Hey, look what I got. I got this lighter. It says big big energy, you know, hey, what's up? Oh, there you are
You can do a flex real quick. I had captain haven't even another flex
No, yeah, look at that. I like it. Wow
He's strong, huh? He is
Wow, so I think his muscles are big. Yeah, I do. Yeah
About an hour a week
I got a natural it's like I you know, I think there's mine. That's like that's that's very much as good
As I get the beaches that way, you know, it's just the way I was it's different than
Else like people do you have it and I used today, but no, I don't you have any muscle at all
No, well Mason. Can you see like how big it is? Isn't that huge? It's there. You go see psyche a little bit of muscle a little bit
Yeah, it's kind of in there
Oh, how about you mason? Are you are you buff?
No, so like yeah, I'm not really buff man. I just a little bit like you know average
Your average, okay
Things I make videos for because like I'm like absolutely idiot
I kind of hit a wall at 200 it when I was first training and then like I was able to get up to 250 at 1.2 70
And then but where I do it is by doing Dorian Yates style workouts
So like he was 5 9 to 80 and he only worked out like an hour to three hours a week
we just eliminate momentum. You just do it very slowly, hold it, and then slowly put it back down
and do one set of failure per each exercise. And you'll find, and then just like for the
rest of the week, just eat tons of food and you'll find yourself growing pretty fast. I gain 70 pounds
Wow, yeah, I can't I don't really gain weight and being six foot three and you know
It's very difficult to fill out. I'm six four, bro
Exactly and I got that then that then bone structure that to mess a more bone structure. I mean, I'm an old hiker
And yeah, I just like you know, I eat when I'm hungry and then it's I burn it right up right off
You know, that's the difference. Yeah, you got to eat on a clock. I will admit that yeah
I mean I would eat every two hours when it would go on either. Oh, yep
It's time for me to eat now pop that you cans of tuna and a potato or a bowl of oatmeal
You know, so yeah, yeah, it's definitely you got to get a lot of calories in and then fats are also very important
Maybe we'll give me give me a few pounds. Yes, my Mason
So Natalie left your channel so she can go on hers and actually go live is what happened
Well, you know, that's great. I mean it's like and I really want to support her
I'm gonna put definitely put her channel on the on the on the psyche verse and I really really want to support my friends
I really do and
Yeah, and untrackable, you know the track was buff to he's a good-looking guy and
He likes to run around in his underwear outside in the rain, right? I've seen him. We do that a couple times
Very impressive, you know all these all these beautiful people around around me, you know
everybody I'm very
You know, I'm very humbled
You attract greatness from others I really do have such wonderful people around me. It's really made it
Me able to survive this kind of big which can be a harsh a harsh universe in the and on the internet a little
You know for the most part just having such wonderful people around me
I'm very very blessed and I I just and that's what I my success is not only about me
It's like you know, I've been helped by so many people
Including all of you and you know, I just want to
the more you surround yourself with successful people, the more success that energy comes to you.
God be careful with who you surround yourself with. Very true. And uh, Alexander that guy,
stand me, he's somebody that you shouldn't surround yourself around for too long just the way he was.
Yeah, you don't want to surround yourself. You know, I, I, Sandman, um, you know, kicked me off his
He's just a jerk, honestly.
He's just a jerk.
Yeah.
And yeah, I won't be going up on his panel again.
Because I prefer to be, you know,
feel like I'm a welcome guest rather than, you know,
how he made me feel so.
But you definitely are all welcome guests.
Thank you for always being on here honestly. I mean you're I would say one of the more consistent
Streamers and I appreciate it
I was telling a friend of mine the other day who doesn't really know about panels, how it works and you know the kinds of people who come on the you know how a panel can go great or it can just completely go wrong.
And she was saying to me she was like it sounds kind of like virtual bars or.
Nightclubs or something like that and I was like they are you're just like a virtual coffee shop
That maybe is a wine bar sometimes
Yeah, especially when I when I started this I was like, you know, I came out of Benning Blanco world and it's like I was like
well, I want to like, you know
Get trashed and like have a party. It's not necessarily
Yeah
I've dealt with a lot of different or, you know, difficult personalities, too
and
You know, I did fall asleep and pass out and get a little I like it better now drinking a lot of coffee, but I like to
Have a couple drinks, but now I'm able to moderate a little bit better, you know
I think I'm I think I am improving a lot in a lot of ways and
Actually, my the show is going in such a direction that I really want to go now
But I did have to go through it like you have to go through it to get through it
I had everything that I've experienced. It's just it's made me a better a better person
Hopefully a more loving person. I never lost the good heart despite anything and also
Think you know, I did I do have a lot of affection even for some people that would be considered trolls
You know as long as people are not doing illegal thing, you know, you know, you know
Going too far, which is not even trolling it when it gets to like this
Cruelty place or you know things like that. I mean there in which it you know
I've seen like a lot of negative negativity. I want to I did come into this especially this universe hoping to be a positive
More positive force and you know and hopefully I'm doing it not always you are doing it
Thank you so much. I'm
I'm uh, I'm trying but firing others. I mean
Because you have such a unique energy and you're very unapologetic, even though you think that you're more apologetic than you are, and I think you should be more unapologetic personally, but you are scaring some people because you're very real, and I know for a fact that you're very real.
You're exactly in person as you are online. Do you have a good heart Alexandra?
Do you have a good heart Alexandra, I would say I'm 50-50 I
Would say she definitely does and I would say you know
I'll say if
If somebody is on her bad side, there's definitely a reason there's definitely a reason and I could I've seen her so
forgiving us, you know, of, you know, and it's like, there's people that I've necessarily maybe was judging a little harshly and then looking at them through her eyes and it's made me, you know, I see that she's very forgiving.
She's very kind, very forgiving and, you know.
Thank you.
I think of just beautiful heart. I think a beautiful heart. I think you're I think you're a little bit hard on yourself sometimes because
Yeah, you're amazing, you know
So you're just a kind person right like overall good hearted person
Yeah, I don't, I wouldn't say it's always in the forefront of my mind to be as kind or as good as I possibly could be, but I do treat others the way I want to be treated. I really do adhere to the golden rule.
But if somebody does something to me, I really think about it and I'm talking about something negative. I think about it.
what should I do in retaliation?
If anything, sometimes in the majority of the time nowadays,
90% of the time, I don't retaliate,
but there's that 10% and that 10%,
I would say would be what my group of critics
is comprised of because when I hit back,
I really hit back.
I don't.
Play so a lot of people are not used to that
They're used to because I'll let the person hit me a few times first because I want to see how they fight
But then I will hit them back to where they cannot get up
So I don't think I'm totally kind hearted because I do I'm naturally a fighter and I'm naturally a bit aggressive
Oh, Sandra, do you work in the office still like you have an office desk and office like chair and computer sometimes
Sometimes I do not all the time CEO of her life. You know, she
Energy, you know
Multi-talented
definitely I was like someone was like I was just like someone was saying
something about oh this person has a good voice I'm like well you know you know
the best the best voice for this is she's sophisticated right like that's what
you think about her I love her boy oh my god I love her voice beautiful yes the
whole the whole the whole package you know
Which I'm not I'm not completely surprised at all that our mutual friend had a thing for it
He has a thing for ladies with darker features like I do and but boy. Oh boy. I mean
I'll tell you why we butted heads. Okay. Um, I I initially
Really liked him and he initially really liked me, but I was not who he wanted me to be and
what you and I'm sure you know this being that you know the world of entertainment directors
are the most difficult people to date because they want to direct you and they want you to do
what they want you to do so dude I mean I mean yeah like straight up my friend I don't know if
My buddy is Kevin Huvane who owns CAA. It's the largest entertainment agency in the world.
You can google his name and see him with nothing but A-list celebrities holding him
like like like Meryl Streep and such and Julia Roberts and I mean he specialized in
female talent but he also does like the Tom Cruise and uh you know Leo and all
every big name you can think of. Kevin Huvane.
All right, we're we're good buddies and we've been friends for almost almost 20 years
But but the thing that he said one day that turned me off to acting
forever
Was he was talking about actors and he was basically like saying like yeah, I'm a puppeteer. They're nothing but harsh puppets
I mean, not those exact words, but that's in a nutshell.
Yeah, and it kind of made me like a little bit like apprehended.
I'm like, dude, you're my friend, are you just,
what the hell are you like?
Cause he was like telling me like not to give his number,
like his home number out to people because he's like,
yeah, then I'd have these fucking, you know,
Horace J-list celebrities call on me and blah and like,
and he went off on it.
I'm like, oh my God.
The way that like, I mean, even like A-list celebrities are looked at by like the power brokers as fucking puppets.
That was the thing, and I'm a puppeteer, like I went to puppetry class, puppetry arts.
And so like, I'm just going, oh my God, like, oh.
Yeah, and be the puppeteer that that's why you know beat us should become a movie director when I think about it
She should she would be very good at that
Mm-hmm. She would be when I really think about it or the green you know
And not in a bit
Series right or I'm having to executive produce a series. It's me. I'm probably gonna get dragged in directing
than I do not want to do right now because I asked Kevin I was like hey
can we bring back this show that used to be really popular I used to work out
with the star of the show it's called greatest American though the greatest
American hero I don't know if you've ever heard of it or seen I know that show
yeah okay so William Cat and I the blonde curly hair guy who was also the
you know from from Kerry the Stephen King movie um and he and he also auditioned for uh with Kurt
Russell you can see his audition with Kurt Russell for Star Wars as Luke Skywalker and Kurt Russell
Han Solo
Kurt Russell's auditioning and he always goes, huh, man Kurt Russell blames me for not getting the hot the part for Han Solo
But anyway, so now we're working on bringing I mean, we've already got next for 2026
We've got six issues of degrees to make the hero coming out. Oh, yeah
We got it. We're good. That is secured
But it's the series that we're working on right now because I want to make a sequel series where he plays
uh like almost like the the the older guy on the original show um like a mentor to the new guy
who gets the suit and if you were to look at my uh twitter you'll see the designs for the the new
suit which i made out of vinyl actually
I'm hoping we don't kill our lead because it doesn't breathe.
But the new costume and everything is an upgrade
from the original because they've tried to make,
they've done three different ABC, Fox, CBS, they've all done,
trying to bring it back.
Two pilots being shot, never aired.
The last one being 2017 the girl from the Indian girl from the the new girl was the one who who played the part it was she was supposed to be this girl who'd like going out doing karaoke and drinking and partying and she gets a suit from the aliens that give her superpowers.
I don't really like that idea. I'm kind of I'm going to go with it's going to be with one of Ralph co workers who gets who he doesn't like at all.
initially, he thinks he's a dumb jock, who's also a guy who served in the military, he's a vet,
who's gonna get the suit and it's like, uh, no, you dummy, I'm not just a jock, I speak six languages,
no, and they're gonna have to work with each other, pair it up, you know, and Ralph's gonna keep
his original suit, I'm not gonna have it taken away from him, like they wanted to do in the 86
he's going to keep a suit, but the new guy's going to get the new one that we've designed,
mostly me, out of vinyl and making it shiny and making it a little more like Henry Cavalesc
and less, you know, Christopher Reeve, you know, William Catt-like style, like the old style,
you know, and we're going to make it look a little bit more modern.
No, you should do well you probably do but but you should document some of that so we can watch it as you're creating. Oh yeah, I've been going along even way before like all this like I was talking to my friends and I say because the whole idea that the thing that made me want to do this is my son.
The birth was not easy my wife my wife almost died in the process and like which is why I'm a little bit like
apprehensive to try to go for another
But anyway, she wants to and you know, she wasn't awake. I was and like I what kept me calm
was watching
A marathon that YouTube actually had playing of the original series
Wow, who's this look at this oh, there's Billy Bob right here
And after my kid was born and stuff and they were resting I'd go out to my to the car and I'd watch it
You know, you know in the car over the the stereo system using that with the surround sound
Just like stay away and watch something it kept me from like having a darn heart attack
And I said, this is a good show, you know, I should bring this back. And right now I'm looking at my computers. We're all like the computer, like the stickers that go along with the computer. Yeah, there's there's a little grace America hero sticker right there.
I remember the big song. What was the song?
I think you should look if all that coincides with the birth of your first child and everything
that you said tells me that this is something that's a part of your soul now and you're passionate
Thank you. Thank you. Yeah, I really hope so. I really do. I mean, I remember when I was friend. I first met William
It was it was a rather funny meeting back in 2004
Before he had kind of come around to liking greatest American hero
Because I had I was a regional manager for LA Fitness and I as well as doing my photographer job
You know, I had to have a regular day job that always get it kept up
So I looked over it in the cardio room and I was
Man, we're asking this guy somewhere before.
Is he like from one of my other gyms?
And like, I was like walking out to him
and then it like smacked me in the face.
Like, no, it's just childhood hero, you moron.
Like, oh my God.
And I, well, I talked to him and like in our talking,
so like, like we went on to like,
go look for weights together and talk.
I said, hey, did you ever ask the production for like,
or did the production ever give you
one of the costumes as a memento?
And he almost like, like angrily said, no.
and I wouldn't have kept one if they did really and I was like oh okay never talked to him about
this again and then it was and then in 2007 like some convention something happened that changed
his heart and changed his mind and he came back a changed man and he's like dude I'm ready to write
let's do this get this going and that's when the 2007 comics were made and then nothing since then
And then, you know, like I said, the birth of my son made me like I told my best buddy, I said, I will die getting this show back getting getting this to come back and I'm going to bug the living crap out of William.
my favorite show my dad's and he created the A team he created a ton of shows back in the 80s
he ruled the 80s man but her favorite show to watch with her dad was the greatest American hero and
so she said I'm on
I'm done game
Sometimes it's like that if the show really resonates with you it or a song or you know any kind of media
If you have the opportunity if people forgot about it to bring it back you should
Cuz it's like that energy trying to live on so you got to acknowledge it
And it's hard. I know Hollywood's so you know so hard and it's like, you know, there's so many
You know things have a life span and sometimes quite short lifespan and so and it's so hard to have that
Success but you know in Hollywood, it's very it's very difficult. So just the level
If you said like family family guy did a parody of the greatest American hero one time like like like like like Peter
dressed up as him and everything it had a wig on and he's like and he's holding on to like a ski rope and
and he's on he's on roller skates and he goes my my same of how is somehow being a very memorable
after a shut run on american tv and then they start they start pulling him and he goes
and and he gets on a ramp and he he's on a ramp that launches him off with his roller skates into
the air and he's flying for a second and then slams of course back in the ground and all his
But it's just like this this show has been kept in the zeitgeist somehow
People have remembered it and when when William goes to these like comic cards. There's a giant line for him
Come on like
So and and my act my action figure of the greatest American hero is the most expensive action figure
I have it's a me go that is still in the box and right now like if you look one if you try to buy one
There's something about $1,200
Okay
Obviously there's some sort of fan interest still there because if it wasn't there wouldn't be worth that much
I'm looking right now at some of the old greatest American hero, you know, pictures and screenshots and whatnot.
Now is a good time for it to come back.
Exactly.
For a lot of reasons, you know, it's a good time.
I just have that song in my head now.
I always liked that song.
And what do you think about this, ma'am?
I have very adamantly said I need two females
on my writing staff because I want to make sure
we keep the romantic comedy aspect part of the show.
That's what people love, yeah.
Exactly, thank you.
Thank you very much.
I'm just saying it's difficult.
You know what?
Because it's the right, it just is.
It's the right time.
There hasn't been
A good show for a while right? Well, I mean I I'm just having flashes in my mind of just
You know seeing the show a little bit in passing when I was young and
like who
If you could pick any
Mainstream actor to play the main character, who would it be?
See that's a good one
Yeah, automatically, I mean I mean at any in the world
It would be Chris 10th worth and not because he's just not because he's his body fits the build and he and he could play a
former a
Combat vet, but because he's got a really good sense of humor
I mean in real life like he's got a distance of humor and I think he'd roll with the punches
You know and he's he's really cool about playing other characters besides just Thor
Yeah, he's very very good about rolling with the punches. My god that does yeah, probably him or our Charlie
And they're both British, which is like what I usually really gets hiring. So, you know, I mean this
Charlie
God, what is his name? Not Hammond, but um
He's also a blonde guys played superheroes a lot. He's from England. He was in the original Queer as Folk
Oh my god. Yeah, anyway, uh, yeah, he'd be a good one too because he's a he's a he's a team player
um, and that's that's I mean like
I don't know if you were asking me but like from working on solo productions that that's the kind of person
I want somebody who can like
That's a good sense of humor the team player and and and it's the physical description not, you know, and I mean like
I don't want any divas
Yeah, I mean you can I wouldn't only focus on like the hair color type because all that kind of stuff
You know here on wardrobe can take care of that as far as you know the look
But um, you're right. It's got to be somebody with
Somebody who's really consistent and very intelligent, but also funny because humor and intelligence those two come go go hand-in-hand
I'm excited
I think it's like if like I could also do like I mean because also we're gonna have more than one guy in the suit
We're gonna have like he's gonna be the main guy
But we're also, we have other characters who have had other suits longer because there are in the, I don't know if you ever really remember the original series or not, but like at one point, like, like, Ralph met a guy who had the suits back in the 30s.
like a real in like not 3d printed but like injection molded and caught like like sewed costume
everything uh miniature for this guy uh blonde hair and like his eyes are completely white but
his costume is black and his cape is red uh so it's different than the other guys costume and stuff
and the the the idea is that for the very first um person they ever gave a suit to
They thought well, why don't we eliminate all of their their their problems, you know like like, you know mortality and being hurt
Well, I actors right how about an AI actor that never had the devil past. They don't have you know, anything
for free
There's
I know I'm gonna incorporate AI, but I don't like that because I do want to hire a person
I'll take a pay cut just we can hire a person and get them, you know some notice I
i'm weird like that um but but but no i also i want this person that like like like one of the
he'll be an anti hero in the show i'm kind of giving some stuff away i've maybe should say
but one of the really cool things about the show is there's going to be an anti hero
and we haven't decided on how old he's going to be i want him to be as old as like maybe a couple
thousand years okay you know and like and and partially insane
Because, because what happens when you live that long, right?
Right? Well, the thing, like, he gets along with our main character and what we got written so far.
You know, this guy gets along with our main character very well so far when they run into each other in the middle of a disaster.
And he's like, how can you see me?
Oh!
I see that thing on your chest.
Yeah, yeah, no wonder.
No wonder you can see me.
Well, anyway, and they start talking
and then they go on a couple of missions together
and in like one of their missions they see,
like you see like like the original guy,
he sees below the ground and he sees girls
kept in a basically a-
Beautiful.
And somebody's-
Psyche.
That looks really like tonight. How are you okay? You don't mind. I have a question real quick
Cannibal fruits
Anyone interrupt me buddy, but go ahead go ahead and go see what do you have to say? Sorry?
I don't think tomorrow's gonna work for me, man. It's either. I'm not taking back my word. I literally I'm gonna
Ever you're available, you know, we can do the ghost
Tonight I promise my brother my little brother and his girlfriend
Whatever you want
Tonight what do you want to say?
Do you want it?
Whenever you want
Yeah
Thank you, sir
Yeah, who is who is Billy Bob psyche? Who's that guy?
They're Billy Bob and chat. I don't know. Is there a panel like a lot of panel Nick Johnson, you know, he's
Do the money right now if you if you guarantee me tonight at 12 o'clock you're gonna be there. We're gonna have another panel
I don't trust you. I don't trust you. I'm just going to wait.
Go it's always
So we agree right like sure. Let's do it. Okay. It's a date site. Yes
Did you know that I was playing that song sugar pie honey, but on her
We can we have we can have the party tomorrow because my little brother I promised him and his girlfriend
We're gonna go to the movies. Oh, I'm just a nice guy. Look at this. Wow
I have to get a little bit. I
Right, let's fucking
Fucking go
Yeah, psyche. I don't know why but psyche. I don't know why but she was playing a song sugar pie, honey
But it's like you know that it was played at on her
You know that I love you. I can't that's all I can't help myself
And you know what? Oh
The purpose long for you Mason
so I can remember that song I remember I remember I remember wow guys I can't help
myself suck you went nobody else you have a great voice though like like sugar I think I
oh honey honey yes especially the bob marley version the bob marley version is awesome candy girl
Yeah, yeah
By the Archies, yeah
Can you show ghosts again in the pink dress on the highway? Oh, you want to see that one again?
Yeah, these are my guys. I have such a cool
I'm gonna put these on the screen like soon
These are like that I have the I somehow found fell into like the hallucinogenic trippy verse on this Instagram
I'm just like if I wish I was on mushrooms right now because I would just be
Enjoy myself way too much. I mean, oh, yeah, so here's the pink woman on the on the highway here. She goes
Hey, I is amazing. There she goes
It's my Aunt Frida
There she is. She's in a high-speed chase Mason
Sike, why is she so big or why she's so wide?
She ate too much way too much, but there she goes
She goes really fast on that little race car though, right?
You can't trust your lying eyes anymore, man.
Your eyes will lie now.
That's true.
Oh, whoa!
OK, I'm going to have to end this dream right now,
because, wow, that's crazy.
Arbiter.
Whoa, $200.
Oh, my God.
Look at this.
Thank you so much.
Wow.
Oh, wow. Thank you very much Mr Arbiter or Miss Arbiter or whatever. Awesome. Thank you. Awesome. Thank you Ghost. Wow.
I really appreciate you and everybody. Thank you so much
This I'm overwhelmed. Thank you
Yeah, it's a good day. It's a great day guys. It's a great day and
Wow
Whoo, you got a big donation psyche
Ghost ghost is a man of his word ghost of his word, you know, and it's like, you know
Just got amazing people around me. I'm just very very
You really do you put a lot of effort into what you do, and I don't think a lot of people
Realize that you're committed to what you're doing completely. I
Yeah, I think I've streamed every day this year except for just maybe I missed three days out of this whole year
And that's pretty impressive to be honest.
Wow.
And people were like,
So that's a big donation.
That is a big donation.
And you know, it's like, people say,
oh, this is like, you know, streaming is like, you know,
oh, it's just, you know, fun.
And it's like, just like playing around
and stuff like that.
And so I, I,
It is it is fun. It is fun. It is a dream come true
But it is it is work, too
And it's like people, you know, it's like basically, you know, every any TV show or any show has like about a hundred people
Working behind the scenes to make make it happen. And it's like a lot in a lot of ways
I have to learn a lot of different roles, but
It's like, I don't do it alone though because it's like, you know, all, all of you guys, all of you, everybody, everybody plays a part in, in bringing the show together and I do this for, I do this for you guys too.
Like, that's like, you know, what brings me back is like, you know, just the wonderful people I meet and it's like, without, without you guys.
Don't know what I'd be doing. You know, so thank you for helping me make my dreams come true because I'm doing what I love
And I can't ask for anything anything more, you know, so just thank you so much
You always get to do what you love
Yes, and may all of me may all of you I wish that for everybody. It's like, you know follow your dreams because
Whatever it is that you that you love it's like you can
You can figure out a way to make it work, you know, it's like if you you know a really it's like the love if the love will bring you
That that's what will motivate you. You know your love of it. And so do something that you love, you know, and then
Yeah, yeah, I wish that for all of you that you all do what you love and
Are able to write and that's just a blessing. I'm
I'm super motivated. I'm just like, you know, I'm speechless. I'm just speechless that I'm just very, very grateful, very grateful.
Thank you so much. Yeah, oh my gosh, you know, uh, wow, Jews do come true, right? Right, Russell?
really focus on what you want to do and who you want to be and
Visualize it and then time if you do that enough you will actualize it
yes the law of attraction is a real thing and it's like I I don't know if it's my
Capricorn to me but you know this Capricorn is this goat wants to climb
that mountain that goat's gonna climb the mountain the goat knows how to climb
the mountain too like and it's a term it's a termination I knew that I could
make this it was just like you know if you know you can do it you believe in
yourself that's like really believe in yourselves and
you can make anything happen.
The main thing is that people just don't believe
things are possible, so they don't even try.
That's why I try different things.
That's why I've tried a million different things.
I've experimented a lot.
I've failed, you know, a lot of things didn't work.
A lot of, some things did work, right?
And it's like, but don't give up on yourself, right?
It's like-
Yeah, never give up on yourself.
Because who's gonna do it?
It's not, I mean, it's like, you gotta believe in yourself.
That's, it's a confident.
Thank you ghost
Thank you so much
Can you play the song one more time if you don't mind if we're gonna play the ghost song this is
Version one or version ghost version one or version two, but whatever yet your panel you think well, I got it right here
You laughed it off said psyche. I'm just me not that dude
You're ready to crash out when the moment feels right
Top donate or energy you light up the night big brother in the chat with that wild grin
Every time you roll in the fun begins. Thank you ghost. I won't forget you
You make me laugh till my face turns blue
Thank you ghost you're one of a kind with your big heart and mischief and you're quick for our mind
You're a positive, positive person, you keep it alive
Dropping jokes in the middle of the late night vibe
You're the spark in the storm, you're the wink in the crowd
Even when you're quiet you're still so
I'll be here every day Thank you ghost. I won't forget you. You make me laugh till my face turns blue.
Psych Paul, man. You're funny as hell. Yeah, it's all over.
Psych, am I not a man of my word? You are a man of your word, guys. It certainly is.
I know everyone here talks. I know what they're going to say, but I am a man of my word, correct?
So I key
Much better now
Just like you have is a video like like like like as one of like the psych theme song or whatever because that's pretty
I enjoyed that
That was that was by the way, I just want to make sure we uh, we were cool
Like I did tell you I was gonna send that I'm not I do have something to do tomorrow if we want to do tonight
I'm down like 12 tonight, but I did promise you them on me and Mike. I sent it on the man of my word
I mean, your ghost or your work, I'm going to create, I'm creating the video now. So then everyone can hear it. Sometimes you can't hear it when I play it on the bang. But which one you want the video of? You like the first song the best, right? The first one, right? Okay. I got it.
I don't know. You should be playing it for tonight, man. We're going to have a party tonight.
Okay, well.
Play whatever you want.
Yeah, I will.
So, the key.
Yes?
Oh, you're talking about the ghost song?
I like the first one.
So I guess so how do you feel now about that? We feel better make them by the way you're invited
Yeah, Mason you're invited to are you gonna make it to the party Mason?
Yes, like yeah. Yeah, you are
Shit, you're not gonna send like you $200 you're talking shit. I just did it
Right and you know that I am a ghost of my word
You are and he's like there is anything like you know, people have fun. Like, uh,
I can't do it tomorrow unless we're gonna do it late. I can do it tonight, but we can do it tomorrow
But it's not be like early hours, but no one joins
Yeah, I did promise my little brother and his girlfriend. We're going to the movies. So
Okay, well whatever whatever is whatever sliver for you and
It's your panel what works for you
Well, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll, I'll
I think that you didn't think that I was actually missing that I did I did because you did yeah you you always keep your worry
You always keep your word. I knew you would I knew in the help you know, we don't agree
Even though we don't agree at all about law. I mean like 90
Thank you. Ghost. Thank you. Ghost. I want to poke at you. Hey, the video is almost ready
I mean
I'm gonna save two more minutes then I can play this video and this is your your video. It's almost ready
It's almost ready. Okay. Hold on one second
I went up and just rendering it and I believe I'll be able to put it up and just
Let's see it
Are we doing tonight? Let's agree. We have to agree on something. We do tonight or tomorrow
Oh, we can do it tonight. Um, I'm 90 percent sure because but you know, um
Unless you know, ld have about like a midnight. Do you hear on midnight? We're gonna have a party those party
Goes tober fast, you know, um, oh the video is almost ready
Guys, so this is though. This is the world premiere of the ghost video
Okay, it's almost there. Okay
Called magic right here, this is just happening really quickly. Okay
Okay
Yeah, I was already having a like a good day. Yeah, I was in a great mood and now, you know
Well, I did that for the coming man of my word also the fish doctor as well. Okay, here comes the video ready for the video
I got the video ready. Okay. Here we go. This is the world premiere
Where am I where am I where is it? Okay? Here we go. This is the ghost video
Yeah, yeah, here we go
Ghosts here we go
Thank you ghost
You cracked the whole panel
You keep it alive
Droppin' jokes in the middle of the late night vibe
You're the spark in the storm
You're the wink in the crowd
Even when you're quiet
You're still so loud
Got that big bro style
Got that easy sway
If I had to choose
You'd be here ever
in your quickfire mind.
From the late night chaos to the morning light
You've been here holding it down just right
If there's a hall of fame for the real and true
I'd carve your name in gold ghost
That's you
I won't forget you
Thank you ghost
Thank you, ghost
Not Tony, huh? All right ghost. I believe you
Maybe
I am a man of my word though. I did promise you that and I did
You are ghost I was all about you
I got a mason sorry mason song. I'm gonna do I
Love uh, oh, yeah, I love the neon priestess, too. I love I love creating songs for my friends because
I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I
Well, I don't think anyway, but you loved it a bit. You do love to be and we had reviler read on and oh wow
That was quite a quite a debate, you know
We found a rum one at 12 o'clock tonight. Did you agree?
Okay. Well, we got to find something to argue about ghost. You know, you love to argue, right? Oh
I love I love it. I'm down there
Listen, you can't listen Alex
Alexander can call me anytime she wants, but you can't call me a dumb dumb, but she can call me any time
By the way, suck yeah, I love you. I appreciate you. Thank you for having a panel. Thank you for being my friend. Thank you for having my back
You know, I I do have your back a lot. You know, I love you man. I mean even though we we disagree about a lot of shit
But you know, I love you man. I love you too. All right. Thank you. Yes
Likey, did I not promise you like a month ago? I think I'm gonna give you $200 soon as my job starts
I'm gonna give you $200. You know, I just I literally just
Likey goes is your good friend, huh? No, he helps you out. When you know, I don't like parking he's a bit shared
You're funny. Oh my god.
We feel like friends, we don't get along about anything.
What's your problem?
I was going to say, like, you know, ghost is going a lot of shit too.
Like, you know, for, you know, because, you know, he is innocent.
He is innocent. But yeah, I mean, shame on anybody that will, like, you know,
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know. I
I don't know. Are you triggered?
What? The cross bothers you?
This? No, not at all, brother.
I think he's just messy.
Oh, okay. Oh, go see. Come on.
You shouldn't wear cross in your neck if you're a part of a tarot card reading.
I don't think...
Oh, my.
I'm still going to wear it. I
mean, I can wear like a
on top of it again.
What if you wear an alien symbol on your chest?
I know, I know. Sometimes I do wear it.
Do you wear a dumb symbol on your chest?
Wait, a what symbol?
Sometimes I'm fucking, no, that's the same logic.
What kind of symbol? I couldn't hear you.
I think we're gonna wrap up the show because I think we have content let's go
Okay, I'm gonna argue with you. Alexandria. Fifty more minutes. Fifty more minutes. It won't hurt my family. Alexandria. We'll have a party.
is that a cross on her neck?
I wear it pretty much every single day. I shower with the cross.
You're making my point for me, by the way.
That's me. I always.
I want one card and I want ten more minutes on this panel if you don't mind.
Alex, Andrew, so why do you wear it cross around your neck?
It's a reminder for me of God and everything
That's a reminder this is American hero captain. I saw it. I saw it
The vinyl costume, you know
Tonight
No, for me across is very important. I have a lot of cross art. I create a lot of cross art
I'm it's just a part of me. I've always had cross jewelry my mom
You know what Jesus said Jesus said judge not list to be judge
Jesus said you know and it's like and so place judgment on anybody that's against
Basically Jesus who is the who's the cross that Jesus is the cross
And a lot of the Christians today, do not really,
I mean, I think Jesus will be scared of a lot of the Christians, right?
It's like, you know, a lot of Christians to be a little judgmental.
Do you know how to do those cards?
Oh, do you want a card to go through an animal card?
I would like a card, but also Mason and Alex, you both invited tonight.
OK.
Where is this channel?
I would like a card though.
On this channel, on this channel.
OK.
That's an animal card.
are you going to it if I'm able to yeah because you got the you are very welcome please you're
a very welcome you got the coyote car today ghost okay this is the well you know I agree with that
Coyote says, transformation, creation, cunning, and good fortune, the coyote often embodies a
trickster, a mischievous, but heroic supernatural being that uses magic, cunning, or deception
to achieve it.
You can tell me in a dumb dumb, because I've paid, I've literally told you I wasn't going
to do it tonight, we're going to have a good panel.
right
Will you please come actually, what are you doing at like midnight tonight? I just be such I most likely will be sleeping
What is it you're definitely not invited you stay up late, Alex Andrew not nowadays lately
Going to sleep pretty early because I wake up really all right Alex. What's your number?
I
The Native American tribes of the Pacific Northwest claim the coyote to be their creator and some legends the coyote forms the different
Peoples of the land from the various sections of a great way
I'm gonna hold you to this. Can you we're making a ghost party?
It's gonna be 12 white, right? Like you're gonna say like
Midnight like Cinderella or it's like, you know
I'm a man of my word you right
But, uh, well, I think, I think I, I think I was the man of my word.
I think it's all to reflect you should be the man of your word.
I will, I said I would.
And I will, I will.
Are you going to join Alexandria too?
Yeah, I think it might be late.
I hope so.
That was pretty cool.
She doesn't like the debate.
She's just cool.
Thank you. I'm not good at thinking on my feet verbally very quickly. I'm not. I'm good at writing, but I'm not.
Go to the back here.
Ghost will debate about whether the sky is blue, whether, you know, like a...
Alex has a question though. If the sky blue or is it fucking blue?
It's pleasantly blue.
Sometimes too
All right, I'm gonna I'm gonna leave it alone
Dude, I literally promised you I got you are gonna
We're going to do it. I got you. I promise. Hey, I got another I got another person
Very disappointed pizza woman at the door again
I mean, it's like, you know, you're just really disappointing the pizza when she's like, well, do you want the pizza?
I was like, is it free?
No, you need to pay cash for it. I said, do you see the bags of manure at the door?
Um, those are the only thing that anybody pre-pays
You know, can I talk to you before I go? I have to get a word. I mean, I'm I go Steve
No, no, no, I'm not leaving. I have one more question. You don't mind. I ask it. I
Want to talk to Alex because don't mind
They don't talk to me like that, but uh, Alex with that cross around your neck obviously your Christian
What do you say you were non?
non
I would say for the most part I'm non-denominational. My main thing is
God is real and I feel Jesus is real. But like they always ask me you know your psyche boy
That's what they were dressed me. You're on here as a woman. You're on here and you listen to the terror reading
What do you think about that?
Oh, here's I feel like he has a solid gift without a doubt. What's up?
LD, how are you doing? What's up, Alex?
LD are you in LA? Yeah, we're driving it. We're driving to Schooner's to meet you. Oh
Schooner it will be their Schooner or later. I'll be invited to my party tonight
Goes I might have to postpone if LD comes into town, you know
You know, I don't know can you send me my $200 back and I can go ahead and postpone that. I mean, I think that's fair
Okay, I'll see you all stream. I'll stream with him. I'll see with LD
Yeah
I'll do IRL with the I'll do IRL with LD and the for sure
Another time
I'm going to crash out. Don't don't worry. Go somewhere you go
All sales are final no hurt. I want my turn back no returns
I
In the fucking blueprint, I want it back now
I think you're kidding. You're just kidding, right?
Now
Let's see if they've got it.
Can I have your chicken?
Oh, it's a it's King Cobra
Oh
If you guys don't mind can I get a piece of OD before I have to go to work? I'll get a what you want to piece of you
We have a meeting
Hey, and I'll put LD on my site too and ghost you better start a channel too and then I'll put you on my site
Two years
You're gonna be on I just said you are I just said you too. Come on ghostie. Hey, look at this
Oh, there you go
I'm just kidding. Anybody want a problem? I'm down to have it
Okay, LD. I don't know your brother, but you look like a couple of my favorite German rappers and like like one of my favorite Ukrainian rappers like
I'm a real slob
By the way, I left my Adidas track suit at home.
Oh my gosh!
I told you they didn't have it.
It's always funny.
Yeah, well, you know how it is.
LD, yeah, Zizio's costume for this entire band is a...
Would you just say the word the audidas? Yeah, it's an audidas track suit, but with his symbol in front of the audidas.
You don't need that.
We'll smoke in the car.
Whatever.
I got the hook up. I know the guy. I know where he lives.
All right, those are my keys. You don't need those
Are you so you're on route? Yeah, dude, we're in we're in what is it orange County?
Long Beach, sorry. Oh, we're in Long Beach. Okay. You can pick me up. Yeah. Yeah, tell everyone your address
Okay, well, everybody already knows it
He's in Redondo
Think my ex-girlfriend let's go friends. They're
They're having a re-unit-ing.
Are they dating?
It's like you're really dating right now.
She's giving me the meanest look.
Ask him.
Re-united.
Re-united, and it feels so good.
I know it has been nice.
It has been nice.
You know, I was worried it might be awkward,
but no, it's been really nice.
It's like I'm home.
Wait till I get a couple drinks in me.
I don't look at awkward.
Oh, my God.
Oh, jeez, that's good.
Are you going to be handsy?
I might get a little handsy.
No.
You guys, you gotta watch back.
Saguya, are they together, man?
Saguya, they must be together, huh?
I think so, I think.
Wow, basically.
They are together in the same hour.
I'm not sure if I had that stream up,
but when it was, because you know,
you did, Mason did have a little,
you know, you said a little threat,
so I had to like take down the stream last night,
but I think I had the clips of when they were doing
some of the,
The POV hotel room stuff. Oh, yeah, I was wearing the mink coat and my pimp my pimp suit
Yeah, he was wearing the key of the cane the coat
Why did you turn quiet that day though? Why were you quiet yesterday when you're on camera and stuff?
You weren't saying anything like you weren't quiet. Oh, there are a lot of people talking so I'm not trying to talk over people. Oh
Yeah, we're so stunning in California, holy shit
They say
Where were you at right now with County? We're in Long Beach. Yeah. Yeah Long Beach. Oh, yeah
You're a little south of here. Yeah. Yeah, it's real nice
The elderly that guy got he was on the stream yesterday when you were on camera with your woman at your width right now
Yeah, God, he got he's a good friend of mine
Yeah
God he's again God. He's a great guy
I guess we're going bar hopping without psych. Oh shit. No, I mean, as long as you pick me up
I can't see the cross streets. Just put your number in the back chat. I'll text you.
I don't want to share my phone number. I don't want to share my phone number. I got to use it
Yeah, what's like the biggest intersection near you okay cross streets are barrel and Elena. Do you know where that is? Oh
Those major cross
and Barrel Street, or PCH, and I'm very near Prospect,
PCH and Prospect, or I thought they don't cross, let me see.
Got where that is?
I know where PCH is.
190 at the PCH.
Yeah, that's the Coastal Highway, I know.
Yeah.
We drove past a little bit ago.
It's like actually you can take the PCH from Long Beach. Just go down PCH until you get to redondo and it's like I'm ready
I can be on PCA, you know and
Yeah, I mean, it's not gonna be that bad right now
Yeah, I'm all good to go. All right. Okay. Yeah, actually you can write psyche at psycheawakens.com
Psyche Awakens. Psyche at Psyche Awakens. Okay.
Yep.com. Yep. Alright.
I'll get right back to you.
As soon as we pick up some In-N-Out, we'll be right on our way.
Alright. Alright.
You know that line's gonna be so long. I know it's gonna take us a few hours to get there in and out
I don't know. I don't know if they're bestie with me or not. I don't know. I'm about to like jump in the shower
Just like uber and meet us yeah, we're going to the gay bars, so
You were telling me about that nice gay bar
What is that one spot like the clown room or something the clown room?
What is that one clown bar in LA?
In like in the south bay. There's one gay bar and it's in um, um, I think hot door in the city of
What about what about the clown bar?
I can't remember jumbo jumbo's clown room jumbo's clown room. Okay jumbo's clown room. We see
It's a strip club. It's a strip club. Yeah, like a male strip club. Oh a female strip club
And they're all just like clowns?
It's like little things in there.
It's a clown theme strip club.
Fuck the bars.
Oh, I want to go to a game.
I want to go to like a Chippendales kind of thing
where I can like, you know,
touch a thaw, a male thaw.
So like, you know, we're all going to have stuff again.
That's a wiener.
Awesome wiener.
Why don't we just come to Long Beach then
because we've got plenty of gay bars.
Yeah, we had a game run. We do, we do. It's down on Broadway. Yeah. Like all the game
shifts over there. We even got Rainbow Crosswalks. It's like, I shit you not. Yeah. Well, Jumbo's
is. Are you going to meet up with them? We'll see what happens. We'll see what happens.
You know, I'm like, I'm a little bit like, you know, my e-bike is kind of out of order
You know, but I'll see what I can do.
Actually, if Uber takes PayPal, I can do it.
Yeah, I can do it, but I think they do actually.
I think they do, because I, yeah, you have to slip off.
So, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so, so
Can LV just buy, can LV buy like a, can you get like a just a G string for yourself and then we don't have to go anywhere?
Why would I need to buy one? I've already got one in my luggage.
Okay, perfect. Perfect.
I got the party, I got the American flag one, you know, the party boy.
He's gonna work out perfect. I just know it.
He's gonna work out perfect.
Yes.
Alright.
Okay, well keep me hit me up if you can but if you mean if you can I understand but yeah, it's thanks for thanks for
Thanks, uh, yeah, yeah, definitely man. Okay. Love you. Wow and
Oh, look at there's a clown.
Oh, there's a Barbie doll.
Oh, there we go.
That's Betty White Doll.
Is it Betty White Doll?
No, that's not it.
It's a Betty White Golden Girls action figure.
Oh, my God.
I have an autographed photo of Betty White.
Oh, wow.
It's a poseable.
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
This is Pennywise the Clown.
Pennywise?
Oh, my God.
Look at you.
Look at what you got.
I, you know, I do, uh, I do have a clown fetish and I'm, I really go. Um, they are, uh, well, Pennywise was kind of hot, but it's only a Tim Burton one. I don't like that, that new one, you know, like the Tim Burton.
Yeah, yeah. Well, you know what they did with that was they tried to make it look more like the, uh, the book because if you look, or if you read the book, you know, the, uh, the original, like, if you, uh, I don't know if you know Bozo's clown, Clarabel.
Yeah.
Well, Bozo's a very creepy looking clown, isn't he?
He is very creepy.
Yeah, I think Bozo would have been enough, but for some reason, Stephen King decided it was supposed to look like Clarabel.
Well, you guys, I'm actually an ascended of Joseph Bromaldi, who was the original clown.
He is the original, the originator of the clown is my relatives.
And so, and I'm not kidding you, he was the original clown.
in France. Yep. Pretty crazy. Um did he insult the king a lot or what did what did he have?
It was very gesture-like. Um it was very gesture-like but it's like it was different from the
gesture because he was kind of uh he was kind of made before. I can just show you a picture of him
too. This is the original clown Joseph Grimaldi um and you can see he had actually would have a
And that's actually the Grimaldi family of Monaco.
Okay, Joseph Grimaldi, let's see, here you go.
Clown, okay, check this out.
This is what he looked like.
Yep, the original clown.
Here we go.
oh interesting that is very moha and he follows the rules too because there are rules to being a
clown like that that john wane gacy specifically broke on purpose well john wane gacy i believe
was a psychological operation because who else could have 33 victims buried under the floor
boards of his house and uh not have it stink to high heaven you know well i don't know i mean
hide the smell but also like John Wayne Gacy if you're if you look at the pogo with a clown costume
there are sharp edges to the mouth there are sharp edges to the eyes those are all no no's
and clowning because sharp edges are scary so we want to make clowns the least scary as possible
so you agree with that he made it the most scary as possible well look at the yeah sharp edges right
I mean not not the captain about the captain. Yeah, check this out here. I was looking for this
Scott David Roy Karch and will oh my god. Yep. Yep. Yep. I recognize. I mean will it that's on the right
Yeah, that's all of us right there
Oh my gosh. Yeah. And I can totally see him. Yeah. Oh, there's Scott. Yeah. On the, on the left. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, yeah. There he is. Yeah. Yeah. That's exactly as I knew them. We had to work with him at the, like, we were, we were probably like, just like barely passing each other. I mean, seriously, I worked with him in like the last
You took me on a blast from the past. I was sitting here looking. I was like,
I got to find one of those pictures and I did. That was from AVN.
Oh, that's surprising. Yeah. Because it wasn't ex-biz. It was the other one. I don't
can't remember the name. But it was one of the awards shows that I'm sitting there and he's
talking about. He will sit right next to me. Jeff.
and he keeps on talking about you don't like Mia something I forget what her name is but she's
very beautiful black girl but she has this very small breast and I was like eh not really into
that but I mean I'm not into her her looks here's um me and Misty
Actually, I think that's the girl he was talking to and Misty. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That's that's the guy who's talking about
Yeah, and I was saying how I would find
She was an amazing performer. I think she's also saying but oh
I got I find in all the pictures. Oh my god
And like I'm like the dark skin guy like I like the girls the darker skin. So like, yeah
Here's more yeah, these are my these are my old days
Who's the lady on the right I wouldn't mind I don't know
But that's me
This guy was always around. I don't remember his name, but that's a bar to lay in the middle. Uh-huh
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
I mean I have forgotten about so much, thank you so much Captain for being on here today
because today's blast from the past, man.
How much fun, it's so much fun watching you guys reminisce.
But I have a, you know, I do
I do know a fan of yours, I've had somebody, a friend of mine, and I won't tell you who
she is on the air or whatever, but I do have a friend and she, you know, she knows that
we're friends and she, you know, she let me know that she really, really, really enjoys
your movies.
Okay.
Yeah.
Like it.
Most people don't.
My sole purpose of being in that world mainly was
To kind of almost be like a diplomat because I if I'm prepared I'm a decent speaker
And I made certain people look very very good, but I wouldn't say I was a good performer
Now I yeah, I
Yeah, I have I don't well
I don't know what I was going to say, but, but, but, but, but it's funny because I like it sometimes you just forget about certain things, but it's good to remember, man, it feels so long ago.
Is it the 90s?
No, 2008 for me, I was in the industry 2008 to about 2012.
That's it. Mm-hmm. That's it, but um, it just feels like a lifetime ago, but it's good
That is I mean it's 15 years. Um, yeah about 15 years ago. I mean, yeah, well, I can't believe time has gone so fast though
It's like it's just crazy. Oh
We were walking in Hollywood psyche. Um, I lived off Franklin near Highland like my old apartment when I was living out there
It was really close to where we were
mm-hmm
So, oh, yeah, I love that. We had a great great time in Hollywood. Wow and
We're gonna do it again. We in December. We got to do some hell. Yeah, yeah
Yeah, that was probably but the highlight of highlight of my you know entire year if not, you know
It was, it was me, you, and uh.
Oh.
You're so sweet.
Oh, I mean, really, I mean.
I'm trying to figure out what we're going to do in December,
because I'm definitely going to come back through in December,
and I'm going to figure out something amazing for us to do.
I haven't really thought about it, but, you know, it'll be something.
You'll have fun, you'll have fun.
OK, let's see.
Yeah, I
I'm just like I'm pretty uh, I want to hug my kitty cat. Hey Rory come here. I'm gonna come here. Oh
I had some crazy time. Thank you so much for reminding me of certain things captain because I needed to revisit a few things in my mind
Captain you're never a performer captain. You were just though you just have the camera
Captain, do you know, do you know a guy named, um, I don't want to say his, he went by.
I was talking to my wife.
I'm having to like handle my wife off.
I mean, I handle my kid off to my wife and stuff.
And she was like freaking out because some of her medicine was out of the refrigerator.
Anyway, sorry.
Sorry, guys.
I was a wait for a second.
I was, I was just telling you, thank you for reminding me of a few things I haven't
thought about for a long time.
Do you know a camera guy known as, um, Maddie?
M.A.T.P. he's been in the industry forever.
Yeah, yeah.
That was who I was in a relationship with
for the most part when I was in the industry.
Oh, wow. Hey, here's a book. I don't know if you guys know this or not.
You know the camera guy that like, he was married to a model in the industry, in the film industry.
And I don't know what happened. I don't know if she did it on camera, if this is to her, or Noy or whatever.
He shot her and killed himself. He was Asian. She was white.
Oh, well, I thought you were taught.
I don't know about that story but there was another situation with a girl from Canada
who died mysteriously and I always thought it was her director boyfriend who did it
and I think he got away with it too. I can't remember what her name was uh uh August Ames.
Do you know about the August Ames situation? Dude that's exactly who I was exactly what I'm talking
No, no, he was
Really and he is something like that was it was Asian. Um, yeah
Because August Aims should not have, I remember that girl, she was gorgeous, oh my God.
August Aims, everybody said committed suicide, I'm sorry, no, no, no, another girl, she looked
at her name, it was like August Aims, but no, no, no, a little shorter.
Yeah, yeah, August, everyone said committed suicide, right?
Because of online police.
Well, supposedly, I don't think that was a suicide.
Yeah, I wouldn't be surprised. Mm-hmm. I don't I don't think it was a suicide. I think that
She was around some really bad people
that's what I always have the feeling about and
There's another girl see there were a lot of girls who all died at the same time and
They tried to make it seem like it was suit, but it didn't feel like suicides. No
No
Well, that's the thing with that with those is like you can't there's not really like a survivor or you know anybody to
To tell you know, it's like, you know, all there is is a body and what looks like, you know
yeah, I think with August it was that guy who
decided that because she didn't really want to be with him and I think he did something to her and
There was another girl. She was her birthday was January 7th. She went by
Her stage name was January
Supposedly she killed herself. I don't buy that one either. There were a few
January, that's an interesting name.
January, Sarah, that's who it was.
She was more of a cam fetish model,
but she was really,
she had a lot of the girls who died
had a similar look to each other too.
Tall, slim, model-esque, statuesque bodies, brunette.
It was a few I remember it like I was writing about it one time was like five girls who all died at once
Oh, I don't like thinking about how many people that I've met have been in playboy. How many like um
I know, you know, two official Playboy bunnies, I think,
or three, not well, it was Trisha Playboy Bunny,
I'm not sure.
She was a cyber girl.
Cyber girl, yeah, because well, Emma Levi-Tim was also,
she was like kind of in the transitory period
between like the internet and the magazine kind of thing,
I think, and it's like where she was considered a bunny,
right, and then it's like, and then Alisa Jordana
was in Playboy.
Yes.
And her name was something Rhonda Shor or something like that.
Then if she looked completely different than she did and then I had a teacher at my school Harbor College
And she was a former playboy bunny
But what is Nick doing? Yeah, let me see who else?
I met a quite a few
quite a few people that have been in playboy and
you know, I
Something with me and gorgeous women. Yeah, I just like it's I just continued to
have to meet them
Well, maybe it's your energy. Maybe it's because you have like a comfortable entertainer energy and you know
Women who are entertainers want to be around
Comfortable entertainer people and I'm very I'm very non-judgmental and
You know, I know there's so much judgment that goes on with that and stuff like that
And so here's me doing a signing at one of the conventions. I forgot about this
Wow
I'm telling you that's why it's like funny to me people are like, oh, I bet she's gonna feel bad if you bring up her porn
Uh-uh
This this was my prime. This was the prime. Look they even made a
Let me show you something you look the same
They made like a thing of skateboard decks with my picture on it. Wow
Those yeah
I'm out. I love it. Yeah, that's my stage. Yeah, you might want to mute him. Yeah, I got it.
Oh, you know, quite a quite a quite a day. Yeah.
How's the chat doing I haven't I'm sorry if I neglected the chat it's harder to see it's harder to see the chat now that I
uh on this peak I don't know I have to make these my uh
Continue bigger, but how's the chat doing? Let's see
Um, how do I fix it? Okay, there we go
Let's see. Oh my god 121 come a Sean a shan troll eliminator. I like that name, uh, Russell
uh
Ostend
Hello everybody, we have a Scarlet Fever,
reality Nancy, Jamie's Cowboys.
Look at control of the minors talking.
Oh, it says Shauna does Dallas, that is Shauna.
Who is Shauna?
Give me an autograph, Shauna, I love you.
Shauna does Washington, Shauna does the planet.
She's a screamer.
My little Shauna mayor, oh my, oh, hold on.
I
What's up psyche hey, Alexandra, how are you doing good? How about you? How's everybody doing today?
I'm good. Just hanging out at psyches today for a few hours. I haven't done that in a while
Well, that's what's up. Oh, yeah
Psycho you did a little IRL this morning, huh, bro? Yeah, I just said you just walk to the McDonald's, you know, it's a little bit
I had a really great show.
Look at Nick's stream of beef cake thing and the,
what did he do?
That's what's up.
What's he doing?
Nick always loves to show off.
He's a great buddy.
One time he accidentally like took his pants down
while looking at the bar when I streamed that.
Uh-oh.
I like it.
Have you ever seen a great joker as Alexandra?
Yeah
I want to show you this real quick because this is like the original the first time
I was ever clipped was after like Jokers was on my show when I just started basically and
You know you can see my face when I think you'll laugh at this
I don't know if it was too hot for YouTube or what let me see I'll do it
Okay
And it was, it's actually tripping, and this was my first clip that I was ever in, I believe, and, well, and now I've been in like, I think, I think I've been in maybe over 10 tripping clips now, oh my god, two days ago, they're, oh, okay, so yeah, I'm actually, oh, it's a tripping, okay, I'm tripping, I'm gonna take a tripping clip.
So if he did a road back mountain kind of thing, oh, here it is, okay, and, oh, you did it again, okay, so this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the, this is the
I
Would have to see it again. I'm not sure what you're talking about. Oh, there you go. Yeah. Yeah
What
Saig's pussy is compulsive
Well, since we're gonna be working together
Rick it's time. We start drinking yet
Your asshole is
Somebody
You want me to take my shirt off?
You know, it could be like this, just like this always.
This thing grabs hold of us in the wrong place, and we're dead.
Boy, it's your fan's way to make the tent pass the deer.
You don't go up there to fish.
You don't know nothing about it.
You know, Flirty Diamond asked to see my wearer in my shirt.
How bad it gets if you can't fix it you've got a standard I wish I knew how to quit you
I need him. I wish I could find it. I wish I knew how to quit. Yeah. I wish I knew how to quit you.
Um, it says. Oh, I need to make sure. Oh yeah, it is. Hey Natalie.
Hi.
Queen
Natalie I can't hear you
Natalie maybe fix your microphone
Natalie what is your YouTube channel name?
It's called
Natalie's um, it's off. It's off. It's called that on my
Right Queen Natalie white we not
Okay, oh
I found you. Yeah, I want to subscribe. There's not many people with that name.
You're the only one. Actually your um numb your your alias your name is karaoke queen 82
karaoke queen 82 if people want to do the at sign
Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh
I think Joe would be down like in real life. I think that would really go down though
I think Joe would be down to give you a good kiss
Oh yeah, there's no more behind the music.
That's right, Kim, but she looks like a giant here,
but she looks like a little boy.
That's his mother or his mom.
Yeah, that's his friend.
He's always like, he's so funny.
He's always like, oh, she's stealing my stuff.
He always looks at a person.
She has all his silverware or something in her bag,
and he's like, oh, you're stealing my silverware.
He steals all his weed.
She takes his weed all the time and his canned goods.
There we go. Yeah. Hey, what's going on Natalie? How are you? Yeah, I'm fine. That's
cool. What are you drinking? What are you scooping on, darling? Pepsi. No, I'm not.
Oh smoking. I'm smoking weed right now out of a vape pen. They come out here. They come they look like this
I'll show you what it looks like it's called
Yeah, no, no, I smoke weed I don't you know smoke anything else
He's called what we call is called og syndicate plug
Are you are are you Indian by any chance? No, I'm Hispanic every I always get that everybody always
Every time I go like to a liquor store
We'll go and start talking to me
They'll start talking to you. I'll be a Farsi and then they're like, I'm like
I'm like, I'm sorry man. I'm not Indian
I'm not
Yeah, no, I'm not Indian I'm Hispanic
My best friend, he looks like, like out here in California, he looks like he is from Sri Lanka.
So I went up to him and I said, how are you?
You know, like, I was just, how are you?
And, and, and, uh, say, how are you?
And he's just looks me like I'm crazy.
That's how we met, you know, the best man at my wedding.
That's cool, yeah.
You know, like, Charlie are really walking in the chocolate
factory, right?
Wasn't it?
Like, one Indian guy played all the oompa-loompas
and looked through it.
There it is, right there.
For no reason, that really works for you.
maybe it's because i'm symmetrical it's not symmetrical and and maybe my face is symmetrical
it's a good whoever made it did a really good job on it for one thing but yeah
can i ask a question can i ask a question about the picture
What is that white stuff on his eyebrows?
And never do not look like the original.
It looks like the master.
I love being an oompa-loompa.
I have issues with that.
I'm calling you the master.
I like you very much.
Yes, I can only wanker.
And I'm his oompa-loompa.
I'm really good. I'm like, I'm Willy Wonka. I'm Jerry Springer. I'm like
He's Howard Stern. He's Jerry Springer. He's uh
more public. He's uh
What a who else? Um, there's a little Russell Brandon psyche. I have been noticing that lately. There you go
There you go doesn't Russell Brandon have a show too? He has a he has a show too getting he have a show like on FX like yeah
Yeah, he's a cool guy like Russell Byrne
He dated Katie Payne for a while
Without the hair, but you look a lot like an actor named Richard Delgado and he played the master
He's the original master from the television series
Dr. Who he's like the big
Oh, okay. Well, I love being a villain. I love being a villain
Like a dark-skinned dark-haired man naturally, you know
The what? I couldn't hear that again. How many people on the panel really think that NASA would send Katy Perry to space?
Well it wasn't NASA, it was a private company.
She went to low Earth orbit, which is still considered space, but you know, whatever.
It wasn't like going to the moon. They didn't go to the moon or nothing like that. They didn't they didn't do no
a ride to space on the big 25 it's not
that woman was selling a fucking soul for a new pair of breast implants
I think I think like the ceiling for a big 25 is something like 60,000 feet and they went way
above that I mean I could be wrong but I mean I know they were way above the ceiling
I'll agree with you. I mean, I like I like the original I kissed a girl by Jill Sobel. Yeah, much better
But yeah, well she first got discovered. Do you know the story on her? She first got discovered by a guy named
Travis
Yeah, yeah, and she was with this guy from Jim class heroes. She was in that music video first and then she got her own
Yes
Sorry. Oh
I think they have gone like really far into space but they haven't told us but that initial
moon landing I think we did go but they did but maybe they inserted some doctored or you
falsified footage just so the media had more?
Everybody points at, as falsified footage,
like, no, that's a wired, I mean,
I have wired capes, like, that's a wired, you know, flag.
That's why it looks the way it does.
It's a wired flag.
One person said, well, how are they able to film them?
Because there's an arm from inside the lunar module
that you click and moves out as a camera on it.
it's really really simple it's not like like like super like science or anything uh that's why you
don't get a great angle of uh of of them and initially I mean you just get them like coming
out of there and it's not like the camera guy follows them right go out and ask him you've got
No
I don't have nothing on over here
Yeah, but it's not coming from me for sure like I just shut down every other tabs
Oh, so brand yeah, yeah to me you look so much like him. It's crazy to me
He's a he's pretty attractive
He's like crazy kind of YouTube channel or he's a bit much. I mean he's very like
He has a rumble contract actually
Because so everything he does is with rumble initially and then it's posted to it to YouTube
Yeah, I've been I mean Russell and I have an interesting relationship
We did not like each other because we guys were like
We we saw each other in mutual parties and stuff initially and he would just like disagree with me so much
And I would even like say hey look a hole like you know
the apex predator and you know
England is a fox, okay? You know, I've been attacked by bears and alligators. All right,
you want to tell me I can't have a gun? Like, so we would just like go back and forth on BS like that.
And then, and then years later, you know, like he kind of comes around and is like,
I see your plate, actually. And I don't know what happened, but he's become a much cooler dude.
I really, really like him now because I used to nothing hate him.
I always liked Russell Brand. I don't know a lot of what he says. I probably don't agree with a lot of what he says, but it's something about just his energy. I always thought it was fun.
Psyche does look like Russell Brand. I'm actually looking at Psyche right now, just like at a glance, and look at his hair. He's got the beard, he's got the height, the same shade, everything. Yeah.
Almost the same kind of look too like like like the same kind of like style of clothing and
I see a little Marcus Schenkenberg in you, a little Jim Carrey, a little Hugh Jackman.
There you go. Hugh Jackman. The Wolverine. Right there.
We all have our celebrity doppelgangers.
Uh-oh, uh-oh. There you go.
Uh-oh, look at Madeline.
accused of multiple counts of things, not just one person.
Hey, Ray, I don't know what you're talking about.
Sean Pika, oh, Sean Combs was a sentence of four years.
That's what the users are now.
Four years?
Yeah, four years.
So another word to nothing?
Yeah, he got away with it.
I knew that was going to happen.
Well, I mean, it's like,
if you get pretty much a follow guy in this situation,
there's probably people that are,
he's probably just in the middle of it.
By the way, I'm looking, sorry.
Did you hear the rumor
about how Chris and Kim Kardashian are next?
No, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I
I'm just saying, though, can you
west where it's been walking around?
I was going to, ah, if O.J. had never,
let's just say maybe committed those murders,
we would never know about the Kardashians.
Very true.
They're not the name.
Well, that was...
But you know what, we're talking about that.
Remember, we were talking about that in Hollywood?
Yeah.
I was not the guilty like I thought the cool simpson was actually like I'm the Kardashian mom in a wig and they were actually best friends
You know supposedly oh, yeah. Oh, yeah
Ray J
Ray J's put that rumor out saying
That there's like an FBI
Ractarian case or something against and she's suing him
for defamation, now that he said that.
Yeah, I think that's probably gonna end up being raging
who goes down, those Kardashians,
you cannot touch them.
I don't know what it was that.
They're very connected.
Yeah.
If I'm connected, they're connected.
I mean, like my body right now of 18 years,
this happens to be the chief of police, Jim McDonald.
I've known him since he was the first assistant chief
I mean, I had a company, I mean, if you look at the movie Fast Glass or Kill Speed, it's the same movie with, I mean, Nick Carter, one of the Backstreet Boys plays a drug dealer in it, but Tom Otto plays a drug cook.
But anyway, back when we were making that movie, we auctioned off rides in our jets, L-39 Albatross fighter jet. You fly in to learn how to fly a fighter jet.
if you're going to be a fighter jet pilot, okay? It looks a lot like a fighter jet except for the
straight wings. That's the only thing that really stands out that makes it look different because
real fighter jets typically have swept wings as they go supersonic. Anyway, so we oxygened off our
rides starting off at 4500 and up and for the LAPD fundraiser True Blue at Paramount Studios on New York Street.
which is the street at the studio and so that's how I got to know them and Jim McDonald but like
that tells you right there like if I'm connected I'm an absolute nobody I'm a nobody here in LA
but when I got pulled over by the LAPD I put Jim's card underneath my ID like he told me to
he told me to do this shit I'm not even playing around
And I hand it to the cop. The cop looks at it and he goes, what's this? And he sees his boss's,
boss's, boss's, boss's name on the card. And he sees this is a real LAPD card. So he goes, what's
that? And I go, oh, I fundraise for the LAPD. I know Jimmy just told me to do that. And he goes,
and the cop goes, have a nice day. Wow. Dang. That's interesting. Okay.
It's like they say it's all about who you know not what you know who you know
Have you ever heard they always say that saying all the time like especially like in the job force like in the workforce
They always say oh
It's not about you could have as many degrees and as many
Circific it because you want but if you don't know the right people and you don't you know
Don't have the right rapport with people
You're not gonna get into that specific field and I learned that the hard way, you know
because I always win against a guy that's always the case but often times it is often it's the case but not
Like Hollywood or like the you know the recording industry stuff like that. Yeah, like show business time
But then that's why they a lot of them you know actresses basically
Did some for prosecution because?
You know
Well, yeah, look at the shit that happened with the what was his name the
That one who got busted that guy was his name the one
They're Mirmax guy. What was his name Harvey Weinstein? Yeah, there you go. There you go
Yeah, look at the stuff that he had them doing just to get the upper step to get a role like and Alex
I don't know
Are you like here's how I look at it, okay?
It does take a certain kind of person to really reach the upper echelons of success in entertainment or whatever industry you're in.
It's not only about, you know, your skill or your talent, but do you have, quote unquote, what it takes?
Yeah, so some, you know, some of these stories that you hear are very negative, but sometimes.
It's positive. Sometimes, you know, what's really wrong with someone who is powerful?
male or female who takes a liking to someone who's struggling and trying to make it and giving them
an upper hand if
You know that person
Vibes with them. I mean, I just like I'm not saying that the person should go after anybody non-consensually
That's wrong. But I mean just look at all the they call them power couples in Hollywood or in business or whatever
To where one of the partners elevated the other one. I think that's just a natural progression of how life goes
I mean, it's always been that way when you look at a royal families or in anyone with money
There's generally someone who enters that equation
Who has something that's not monetary that's a benefit to the person who does have the money, you know, maybe it's a poor actress who ends up with a director who is looking for a really skilled actress and they happen to fall in love.
I don't think it's always a bad thing when that happens, but you know, that's my yeah. Yeah, very true.
Hollywood, like brutal, brutal industry, I think, and people who are willing to do anything and there's also this power dynamic, too.
You think about Michael Jackson, right? Think about the power he has talking to this, like, you know, the Wade Johnson, whatever.
This family, poor family from Australia, he basically said, okay, I'll give you $4 million if I can just take your son on my tour with me.
basically let them on behind you know and it's like and that's kind of like a really big imbalance
of power and it's thinking about how different you also have to remember something about Michael
Jackson I I mean my buddy one of my buddies how he's Klein he's the president of Warner Brothers
um music uh and he he talks a lot of snack about Michael Jackson and um I've heard other people
who work with him and all that sort of stuff and from what I've been able to make make out is that
He was a dad, a business, I mean he was his perpetual victim and to him money, just like
me, money is just like, whatever, it's a mean to an end.
What matters is like people.
So if he really liked this kid, he thought that this kid was a great act and wanted to
elevate this kid.
He goes, hey, I'll tell you.
I'll pay the, you know, the parents, you know,
four million dollars is kind of like,
let this kid like half his own life.
I can see that.
I can see him going, you know, I'll pay the parents,
that way they'll butt out
and they won't do what my dad did to me.
It's what Michael could have thought.
Well, he was a victim, but he was also,
like a very savvy businessman
because, you know, he was best friends with Paul McCartney
and Paul McCartney gave him some business advice about,
you know, he's like, oh, you want to get a picture of him?
by a music catalog, and he taught Billy under Paul McCartney.
He bought the Beatles, the New York catalog,
under Paul McCartney, outbid it.
And then he's like, excuse me, well, that's what he said.
Well, Paul basically told him to do it.
Yeah, he told him how to do it.
And then Michael took his advice and just
put use it against them.
And then like, yeah, it's like, wait a minute,
but you're my older friend who's been around in the business
as an adult longer than me, and you're telling me to do this.
And now I did it, and now you call me a backstabber?
I'm not saying Michael Jackson was a great guy, but I totally understand a boost of showbiz parents
and executives
Sadly I've become like I mean like
Like I said, my buddy Howie was a really executive and talked shit about him.
You don't have a child to go if you're if you're working if you're like basically supporting your entire family as a child
You know the show but his family and stuff like that
And so just all the pressure he's never it was like there really isn't a child that you're working and he was working hard
Right. I'm sure you just like work to the bone just dancing dancing dancing
And it's like work work time for toys and play and stuff like that it's just like you probably have so much pressure
Put on him at that young age
But he could, maybe.
Yeah, and so the reason I sympathize with that
is because I was on Star Trek as a little kid.
It's not playing a big role or anything.
It would just be in the episodes that Alexander
Ryzenko, Worst Kid, was in.
Because I played a class in a wharf and then you know like I got to be on like the
Star Trek set a whole bunch over the years and that I was on a show called in the heat of the night where I worked
The Carol O'Connor I had no idea who the fuck he was but as a kid. I mean, I didn't know I had no idea about our
I didn't even see all the family or Archie Bunker. No idea. I just looked at him as like almost grandpa like a kid with that
And so, um, like, and, and, and coming away from it, my mother, by the way, saw all my money.
Oh, shit.
Yeah, the cougar that didn't like help me out because like even like I actually met another actress who.
She was on iCarly. She was thinking the blonde girl on iCarly. She was not the main star. She was like her best friend, and when she went to go look at her accounts and stuff, Sag did not do their job, the Kugan act, everything, there was nothing there.
There was not a single cent there from Sag. Her mom had taken it all.
And so it's it's it's not like the Kugan act did everything to save every child actor. Another thing is the kid from ET is there was a movie of Elliott, but you know, anyway, he was a neighbor of mine for about 10 years.
Henry is his name.
Every year I get maybe like enough to cover my months one month
That's it. I don't
And he told me he got paid scale
Minimum wage as an actor to be in that movie
You know, a lot of times I think somehow directors know stuff and they're going to blow up because there have been so many people who are like actors and actresses.
I think a lot of times the actresses and actresses, they're enlightened.
This is so cool.
Wow, it's the yeah think about their child labor laws for like pretty much every you know kind of industry except for Hollywood
You know and they say oh
Like one role, but it's still like
A lot of work even that and then the parents and all the money
18 years of that usually
And there's even what's even worse is live performers because like I think the Carter family like I told you guys
I made it with Nick Carter. I made a lot of money off of Nick
I saw his brother, his little brother Aaron Carter
because my uncles had the merchandise distribution rights for a large part of the country.
Really?
Yeah, like a territory. And so I was for a while, like on tour, like as a kid,
he was only about a year younger than me, or two. I was on tour with Aaron Carter as a teen,
and like, and the backstreet boys and insane-
uh every summer i mean so this this made me particularly popular with the girls at my school
i bet but like mostly white girls i was uh i i like black girls uh well the ethnicity
doesn't matter it doesn't matter i don't say that to me i i mean i was i i just did not find white
girls attractive i was wasn't he broke like he was broke by the time he was you know in his in
Yep, after not another, yep, yep, yep.
Okay, so what happened was we did the not another earthquake tour, and he did pretty well on that, which we and the previous tour he did really well so this kid should not have a single problem with money.
I mean, I mean, oh, it was his parents, they took his money.
Yep, it was his mother, it was his mother that took everything.
Well, let's just go and order her daughter that did a show on E with Aaron committed suicide and then Aaron committed suicide about a year and a half ago really, really bothered me.
Do you think it's S-U-S-E-I-D-E?
Do you think that's what, oh is it? Like, I think I thought he's like just overdosing the bastard or something.
Oh no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
it was it was he was so like I can't tell you like the yeah if you've ever been
I was in a band and like if you've ever been in front of the whole but like like
50 to 70 thousand people performing the like the high you get from that shit is
like heroin can't compare I'm telling ya
like it really can't like you just get this high from being on stage in front of this giant audience.
It's mass consciousness that you're feeling even busted.
Look up the busted the year 3000 they just did.
a like over the summer a performance in front of like probably I mean they're out like I said
their average audience is 50 to 70 thousand Americans don't know who they are my buddy is
the lead singer is that they're called busted it's a really giant like almost like rock boy band
around the world. But the one place they didn't want to get put out was in America because
Charlie can walk down the street and unless it's in Beverly Hills, nobody bothers him.
But if it's in Tokyo or if it's in London, oh, holy fuck, he's got to have bodyguards, you know?
It's a very weird existence. Well, the thing is I mean when you become famous
Like the more that people think about you or know about you you actually feel that mass
Conscious energy and you can almost look like if you watch somebody as they're becoming famous
They they you you can witness them feel it
And then they do, as they're adjusting to that energy, some people cannot adjust to it. But if you
have that ability to adjust to it, that is how you ride that wave of famous light learning how to
surf. And eventually, if you're good enough at it, that's how you end up with those mega stars and
stuff. But the people who go through, they can, I don't mean to blow smoke up psyche's ass right now,
As psyche is becoming more popular, he's feeling it and we get to watch it happen.
He's going through the growing pains right now and it hurts. I'm just wondering how much
well the buddy that um that like the guy I'm mainly friends with Charlie he
auditioned like he just saw an ad in the literal free newspaper and back in like
2000 or 1998 or something like I can't remember what year it was but he saw an
ad in the newspaper and he went and auditioned for this band
and holy shit they took off and they became this multi platinum band even the Jonas brothers have covered them here in America that means anything to you guys
they have a song called the year 3000 and at their concerts like what was I thought was just really really fucking cool because they were able to get Christopher Lloyd in the back of the future time machine to go
And it shows like before they start playing the song it's projected on the big screen. It goes, oh, we're in the year, the year 3000.
And he's in the whole, you know, back in the future time machine and everything and all of a sudden the band starts playing the song.
It's called Year 3000.
That's a good question.
Fun song.
Yeah, I'm Bobby Brown jr. And when you Houston bath tub bath tub things right in the Aaron Carter bathtub thing
What is with this like in the bathtub? And it's kind of very strange circumstances for everything. It's a really simple thing
Well, I if they weren't all murdered
it's really simple because I took pharmacology by the way. You take a medication and you feel
like you want to relax, right? But you're not relaxed enough so you go out to the hot tub only
they sunk below the line.
And the, the medications kept them where they didn't wake up and they kept the signal from, from the brain to the body to, hey, wake up, you're not, you're not, you're not breathing right, which is what people with sleep apnea have.
You know, like, like that little signal wakes them up and that's why they always feel tired is because that thing is waking them up, keeping them alive, but it makes them feel tired.
So, in essence, yeah, that could be the reason.
It could be murder, but it could be just that they're not getting that signal to their brains
Hey, wake up and move because they went to the bathtub with it
They took Xanax. They took clop and along with maybe some other drugs and that
stops that signal from the brain to the body
Yeah, well, you know, I think it's a very dangerous hazardous
Life and it's like, you know, there's probably like a lot of pressure and a lot of
Drugs and a lot of stuff being handed out for free and you know temptation and you know over over indulgence and
Just imagine all those
Floating in the air, right? Oh, it's my rainbow. Okay. There's rainbows on the wall. It looks I was like what the hell is that?
Whoa, it's something coming to get you
Yeah, it looks like I thought was like a little like bug or something
But you know, yeah, it's like it's just a rainbow
But it could the green on the rainbow turns black with the green screen. So crazy
I was I was just holding a bottle of morphine sulfate for you guys to see because like yeah, like I mean
but like um you know like if I can get morphine sulfate and you know dilated for crying out
which is basically heroin what what drugs are like some big stars getting who have what they
call concierge doctors you pay like a hundred grand oh they're getting everything you know
Right. Oh my gosh, just like a oh my look at Michael Jackson was getting like prescribed anesthesia like you know
Like that was how he got high just like I could just put hook me up to an IV of anesthesia
He didn't really get high I actually um
It's funny medicine that knocks him out is the only thing that seems to knock me out and and really really really high high high
Doses because they took my other drug with it. It's not me out during surgery
I'm gonna wait during surgery. Okay
The woman that I see now the anesthesiologist I have
Taste the biscuit